Karen Bee
Part Seven
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Seven
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Seven
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Seven
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Seven
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Seven
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Seven
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Scene No. 393
Scene No. 396
Scene No.  398
Scene 402 B
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Nisemonogatari
Karen Bee
Bee
To Be Continued
Xem Trước
Script: Nisio Isin
Illustrations: Haritama Hiroki
We're the fire sisters!
Hey! There's a
crook in town!
Hahaha, I'll trick
you out of
your money again!
Have you repented?!
I'll go apologize to the people I've wronged.
Fraud Diary
Do you know
this girl?
Who's this pure honest girl?
Do you know?
I'll ask Gahara
Next Episode
Tsukihi Phoenix    Part One
It was Senjōgahara Hitagi...