Playing nice
for Hanekawa.
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
When it comes to comparing the Araragi sisters—the Fire Sisters—it's undeniable that Karen, who does the fighting, attracts more attention.
However, that gives the false impression that Tsukihi is the good little sister, and I want to avoid that.
Back in the days when Karen and Tsukihi and I were in elementary school, I recall that Karen got into some kind of trouble.
They weren't called the Fire Sisters back then, and they often acted separately.
In any case, something happened, and Karen got cornered.
Tsukihi jumped off the roof of the school without hesitation to save her.
I don't know if it was luck or if she'd calculated it precisely, but she landed on the roof of a truck that was parked there by chance.
(What is this, a kung-fu movie?)
She survived, but her image as a mature, introverted person was ruined in a flash.
(Of course, she broke several bones, and still has the scars from her "honor wounds", as she prefers to call them)
I was really surprised when she didn't lose a single friend due to that.
Anyway.
Tsukihi is extreme, and she's capable of suppressing that extremity without being aware of it.
This means that whenever she throws a fit, it isn't simply histrionics, but her running wild intentionally.
She runs wild intentionally.
Is something so dangerous even possible?
The problem, then, lies not in her throwing fits, but in the true wildness lying behind them.
That is the essence of who she truly is.
Reference
Nisemonogatari, Book 1
Chapter Six
Karen Bee
"Just sit down on the bed."
"Araragi, you shouldn't just tell girls
to sit on your bed like that."
"Huh? Why not?"
Chapter Six
Karen Bee
Sengoku told me to sit on the bed as well.
To be exact, she told me I couldn't sit anywhere else.
I remember, and sit down in my chair.
"By the way, Hanekawa, why are you wearing your uniform
this late at night?
Chapter Six
Karen Bee
Right. I wanted to comment on it,
but I couldn't find the chance.
Chapter Six
Karen Bee
Hanekawa Tsubasa is always in her uniform.
"I'm used to you wearing your uniform during summer break,
Chapter Six
Karen Bee
so it's fine, but... Don't you have any other clothes?
I've never seen you wearing anything else!"
Chapter Six
Karen Bee
"Haven't you seen me in my pajamas?"
"Pajamas don't count."
To be honest, I've also seen her in her underwear,
but then again, that doesn't count either. I'd rather see
what kind of outfit Hanekawa would pick for going out somewhere!
When can I see that?
"Well, it was just by chance, but I met with Karen this evening,
Chapter Six
Karen Bee
and then came here. Should I start the story from there?"
Chapter Six
Karen Bee
"Yeah, please."
Nisemonogatari 1
Chapter
Six
Karen Bee
"Yeah, please."
She's still
class president,
you know.