Body
Uterus
Fundus
Ovary
Fallopian tube
Ampulla
Isthmus
Fimbriae
Myometrium
Uterine cervix
Cervix
Vagina
Uterus
Fundus
Ovary
Fallopian tube
Ampulla
Isthmus
Fimbriae
Myometrium
Uterine cervix
Cervix
Vagina
Womb
Araragi Tsukihi
Her hair is growing way too fast.
Now that I think about it, that's the reason why she can completely change her hairstyle every few months without using wigs.
She had a bob cut until just recently, now it reaches her shoulders— it's longer than my hair.
How can her bangs grow down to her shoulder in just a month?
Back to the point, Kanbaru's hair grows fast because of her erotic style— but this isn't the time where such a joke could explain anything.
I can't laugh at it. That speed is unnatural. Regeneration ability. Of course cutting her hair has no effect on her life at all, so the regeneration isn't that drastic, but still... Following this idea of renewal, her nails must grow really fast as well.
Her metabolism is just too good.
Even today, she took a shower during the day, and I thought that she's really cutting her nails a lot...
Although it's just a minor episode, nothing that would cause suspicion or even raise attention.
But there are too many of such episodes. There are just too many.
In the end, I just tried to look away, because she's my family.
It won't feel out of place until you realize that it's out of place.
The impostor is an impostor because it can't be distinguished from the real thing.
The proof of its falsity is in its resemblance to the real thing.
Hey
No Entry
Emergency Exit
Huh?
Shinto Studies
Student
Building
Gallery
Social Work Department
Cafeteria
Campus Map
Unlimited Rulebook
A rulebook mostly filled with exceptions.
End