Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số     Không Có
A
Ong Karen
Phần Năm
Tập Năm
Phông chữ dùng cho minh họa: Gentium (Basic) và VL DellaRobbia BT
A
Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số     Không Có
Khung Hình Đỏ
Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số     Không Có
Xem Trước
Nguyên tác: Nisio Isin
Minh họa: Haritama Hiroki
We're the fire sisters!
compared to the
characters who
changed their
appearance
I feel like I don't stand out much
That's not true.
To make the most of my
strong points,
I'll go learn under a karate master.
What bringing
this on?
Roar
Waterfall
Bear
Grr
Mountain
I was too naive!
It's going to air soon!
I'll shave off one
eyebrow and get
myself
psyched up!
What?!
Razor!
Kỳ Tới
Ong Karen         Phần Sáu
We're the new-look sisters!