Cancel
playback
Replay
By title
o=o
By artist
New songs
o=o
Genre
Duet
o=o
Back then
Raw playback
o=o
Guide vocal
Artist's video
o=o
kaicho - a written masterpiece
kaichou - 1) exhibit a Buddhist image (by opening the doors of the sanctuary) 2) hold a gambling party
kaichou - 1) harmony 2) (a) harmony; (a) melody
gaichou - a harmful bird
kaichin - state, express
kaitsuu - open for traffic
kaidzuka - a shell mound; a kitchen midden
kaitsuke - buying; purchasing
kaitsuburi - a little grebe; a dabchick
kaitsumamu - sum up; summarize
kaite - buyer
kaitei - a revision
kaiteki - comfortable
kaitetsu - shingled iron
kare-eda: a withered (dead) branch
kare-obana: withered eulalia grass (appears in Basho's works among others)
kare-gashi: phrase used for persons who need not be named
kare-gata: the time of separation in a relationship
kare-gare: the withering of plants
kare-ki: a dead (withered) tree
* ni hana: if wishes were horses,
* mo yama no nigiwai: anything is better than nothing
ga-reki: debris; rubble
gareki-gaku: phenology
Akasegawa
Bank of Damaged Goods
10,000
Yen
Counterfeit
Bank Note
Ten Thousand
Akasegawa
Bank of Damaged Goods
10,000
Yen
Ten Thousand
Counterfeit
Bank Note
Akasegawa
Ten Thousand
Counterfeit
Bank Note
10,000
Yen
Bank of Damaged Goods
Akasegawa
Ten Thousand
Counterfeit
Bank Note
10,000
Yen
Bank of Damaged Goods
3,000,000 Yen
Time  Temperature   Menu
Start
Manual
setting
Cancel
Favorites
Measure
dish
Finish
Manual
Auto
Water
Microwave
Oven
Grill
Heated steam
Steam
Health
mode
Don't push
this button
My brother saw me
completely naked and now
I'm so embarrassed.
–Karen
Sold
Out
First Love
¥248
New Product!
Love
¥298
Sold
Out
Talent
¥284
Love
¥298
Tax Included