The Dying Bird,
a type of supernatural cuckoo.
A cuckoo as in the poem, "Green leaves, cuckoos in the mountains, the season's first bonito."
Though they had spouted some nonsense about it being a phoenix.
This bird habitually plants its eggs in other birds' nests.
It will wait for the mother of another species to leave the nest,
and pushes her eggs out of the nest, onto the ground.
Then it lays its own eggs for the mother bird to warm and hatch.
The Dying Bird, a supernatural cuckoo,
exhibits this same behavior.
It does the same thing.
It plants its egg in a human nest.
Then, inside the womb of the mother,
it reincarnates itself like a phoenix, the immortal bird.
The common legend of the phoenix
describes a bird at the end of its life,
throwing itself into the flames in order to be reborn.
Here though, the flames are replaced with a human mother.
To be precise, the Dying Bird's victim is not your sister,
but is actually your mother.
So, over ten years ago,
your mother was carrying a monster in her womb.
Body
Uterus
Fundus
Ovary
Fallopian tube
Ampulla
Isthmus
Fimbriae
Myometrium
Uterine cervix
Cervix
Vagina
Uterus
Fundus
Ovary
Fallopian tube
Ampulla
Isthmus
Fimbriae
Myometrium
Uterine cervix
Cervix
Vagina
Womb
And a year later, Araragi Tsukihi was born.
The Dying Bird was reborn.
It's fairly harmless, in the grand scheme of things.
It won't ever hurt anyone.
But it is an impostor.
And it is immortal.
Any wound heals.
Any illness vanishes.
It lives out its lifespan.
Then it dies and is again reborn.
It has repeated this cycle up to the modern era.
Just like the cuckoos.
Come on!
Impostory
Together now!
When I look at the world covered in a sheet of snow
I take a single step forward
The passion in my heart will never change, never wane
Let's dance to its beat
The moon I found that day while riding on your back
looks like a mirror again today, up there in the starlit sky
and glitters with little flashes of light
Some things will change
But some things never change
Though I may be fickle
for the first time, I now know of eternity
and pledge it to you
I'm platinum happy
but I still get platinum sad
and shed platinum tears
Why? Just why?
Discothèque
Araragi Tsukihi
Her hair is growing way too fast.
Now that I think about it, that's the reason why she can completely change her hairstyle every few months without using wigs.
She had a bob cut until just recently, now it reaches her shoulders— it's longer than my hair.
How can her bangs grow down to her shoulder in just a month?
Back to the point, Kanbaru's hair grows fast because of her erotic style— but this isn't the time where such a joke could explain anything.
I can't laugh at it. That speed is unnatural. Regeneration ability. Of course cutting her hair has no effect on her life at all, so the regeneration isn't that drastic, but still... Following this idea of renewal, her nails must grow really fast as well.
Her metabolism is just too good.
Even today, she took a shower during the day, and I thought that she's really cutting her nails a lot...
Although it's just a minor episode, nothing that would cause suspicion or even raise attention.
But there are too many of such episodes. There are just too many.
In the end, I just tried to look away, because she's my family.
It won't feel out of place until you realize that it's out of place.
The impostor is an impostor because it can't be distinguished from the real thing.
The proof of its falsity is in its resemblance to the real thing.
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Four
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Four
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Four
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Four
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Four
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Four
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Four
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Nii-chan, what is this?!
What happened?
An artillery strike? Have syndicate pursuit teams fired a cannon at us?
Honestly, well...
I don't know.
I went to Mister Donut to take a break,
and it was like this when I got back.
Maybe a dump truck hit the house and took off.
So you've been standing guard...
Good work!
But you haven't gotten to study at all today, have you?
I guess not.
Okay, Nii-chan, then I'll take over!
Now it's my turn.
Until Mom and Dad get home,
I shall be Cerberus, the Guardian of Hell.
So get back to your room and study.
Huh?
By the way, where's Tsukihi-chan?
I think she was on the second floor when it happened.
She watched the front until I came home.
She was here when it happened though,
so it was a big shock for her.
She's out cold upstairs.
Yeah...
She does get rattled pretty easily.
I'm sure you want to ask her about it,
but she really is fast asleep.
So let her rest for a while.
Aye aye!
Karen-chan?
What is it, Nii-chan?
Would you be able to die for me?
Sure could.
Why?
Then could you also die for Tsukihi-chan?
I could.
With a smile on my face.
She's my little sister.
Of course I could.
Yeah, of course.
And I'd die for you two, as well.
Again and again,
like an immortal Dracula,
Red
Unnumbered Cut
every day until I was dead for good.
Red
Unnumbered Cut
Immortal, huh?
Not a vampire,
but a phoenix, huh?
It's all so sudden...
I can't keep up with everything.
Hey.
Hey
Black
Unnumbered Cut
What are you doing?!
I can't believe it...
This can't be happening!
My first kiss...
I was going to give it to Rosokuzawa-kun!
What's so funny?!
Nothing...
I was just thinking that I felt nothing when I kissed you.
It wasn't exciting, and I didn't enjoy it.
You really are my sister.
Tsukihi-chan, did you know that there was a time when I wasn't your brother?
What are you talking about?
There was a time when I wasn't Karen-chan's brother, either.
For the first three years of my life, I was an only child.
And the year after that, I only had one sister.
It was four years before I finally became your brother.
Well, yeah...
But, Tsukihi-chan...
Araragi Tsukihi was my little sister from the moment she was born.
My little sister, as well as Karen-chan's little sister.
There wasn't even a second that she wasn't.
Don't count my kiss.
That's how family works.
For example, when we were little, how many times did we say we were gonna get married?
I couldn't tell you.
'Course, I'd have married you both.
Stupid.
You think you can fool me by bringing up the past?
White
Unnumbered Cut
I'm platinum mad.
Hey, Karen-chan.
I'm going out for a bit.
Okay, bye.
While I'm gone, keep an eye out.
No one gets in.
Leave it to me.
Karen-chan does whatever her brother says.
You're going, my master?
Yes, I am.
Where? To do what?
To them. To fight.
Why?
For my sister.
What is there to gain?
Nothing at all.
I'll only waste some time.
I see.
Tsukihi, was it?
The smallest little sister.
Yeah...
What? You learned her name?
It's rare for you to learn a human's name.
Not after hearing you scream it so many times.
And it's a good name.
A good name?
Is it?
I like the "tsuki" part. The moon.
The sun is my enemy, but the moon has been quite good to me.
And so, perhaps now is the time for me to repay it.
Okay.
Thanks.
No need to thank me.
No Entry
Emergency Exit
Uninvited guests...
Oshino-kun would probably say, "Oh, you're late.
I've been waiting for ye."
But I'm no' that friendly.
Oshino...
Oshino never once put out bloodlust like this.
I'm sure that's true!
That's how he was...
That's how it is with him.
So what do we do?
An outright brawl is fine with us.
Simple as can be.
We're all about violence.
And thankfully, both of our teams include a human and an oddity.
There's you and me,
then there's the former Heart-under-blade and Yotsugi-chan.
How does that pairing sound tae ye?
Not happy?
Then, I can take the former Heart-under-blade,
and ye can have Yotsugi.
She is the one who attacked yer sister after all, impostor or no.
No, the first pairing is better.
Excellent.
Then, girl,
come downstairs.
There's a perfect room on the second floor for us to fight in.
We can enjoy ourselves there.
I'll show you the difference that years of experience make.
Sure, that's fine.
Even after powering up, you're still weaker than I am.
Respect for the Elderly Day is still a month from now.
But if you're willing to force that tired old body to show me the difference in our experience,
I'll go with you,
Grannie.
I said, with a posed look.
You're a minor Far Eastern demon,
with nothing even written about you.
I'm going to wipe the floor with that posed look of yours.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Well, I'm off to do some volunteer work for the elderly, Onee-chan.
I said, with a posed look.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Kagenui-san, what's your relationship to Oshino?
How do you know the idiot in the Hawaiian shirt, Oshino Meme?
Huh?
What? Oshino-kun's still wearing those shirts?
I thought it was just some kind of trademark,
but if he's still doing it, perhaps there's a deeper reason...
Well, it's nothing really.
Just an old friend.
Oshino-kun, Kaiki-kun, and I
were all in the same year at college.
Oshino, okay...
But Kaiki?
Kaiki?
That Kaiki?
Kaiki...
You mean Kaiki Deishuu?
Shinto Studies
Student
Building
Gallery
Social Work Department
Cafeteria
That's right. Kaiki-kun.
We shared a major and were in the same club.
Campus Map
We used tae play four-person shogi with an upperclassman.
Was it the shogi research club?
No, the occult research club.
Actually, it was Kaiki-kun who was kind enough tae tell us that yer sister
was our kind of prey.
Kaiki!
So this was all your fault?
It was all your doing?!
Kagenui-san.
I'm on my sister's side here.
Yer sister is an impostor.
She's not even yer real sister.
Even if ye recognize that the sister ye believed tae be real is not,
can ye truly love her as ye always have?
I can.
No, I'll love her even more.
Isn't it hotter if you
have a sister who isn't blood related?!
I understand yer feelings.
I suppose I must respect them.
But from the perspective of a good guy like me...
Nothing I say will change yer mind.
I've given up trying tae convince ye.
I'm different from Oshino-kun and Kaiki-kun, after all.
I can only speak with my fists.
But... But...
I wonder.
Even if you're all right with it...
Even if you're all right with it,
what about the rest of yer family?!
Ye were once immortal.
So perhaps ye'd be fine with an immortal creature pretending tae be yer sister.
But how about the rest of yer family? Those who have nothing tae do with the supernatural?
For example, Karen-chan, was it?
If she knew her little sister was a supernatural creature,
would she answer the same way?
How about yer mother?
If she knew that she braved labor pains for a monster,
would she say the same thing as ye did?
And what of yer father?!
And what about her?
If the impostor knew,
would she be able tae continue living like she always has?
It's all good now because she doesn't know.
But when she finds out,
will she no' be hurt?
An immortal monster cannot adapt tae its surroundings.
Ye should know that better than anyone.
Or will she try tae be a hero, with her inhuman body?
The Fire Sisters, wasn't it?
But how proud, how cruel
might an immortal monster be toward humans?
Ye know that better than anyone, as well!
Our job is tae stop it before that happens.
Whatever ye value...
What ye consider right is up tae you.
But don't force it onto other people!
I'm not finished yet.
I'm starting tae worry about Yotsugi, also.
Let's go take a look!
What are you doing,
my master?
What? For all her big talk, this is as far as she got?
Looks like you're having a tough time, Yotsugi.
I was preparing to stage a dramatic comeback.
Don't worry about me when you don't have to, Onee-chan.
I said, with a posed look.
Right, right.
But allow yer sister tae have this pleasure.
Former Heart-under-blade,
want tae have a final round with me?
No, I won't fight.
And a final round?
Don't be stupid, human.
My master hasn't lost to the likes of you yet.
Correct, my master?
That's right.
I haven't lost yet...
I haven't conceded to you yet.
Not to your fists
or to your words.
I haven't accepted either!
Didn't ye listen tae me?
Whatever ye value...
What ye consider right is up tae you.
But don't force those ideals onto others.
It isn't just "others."
Not "others."
It's my family.
I'll force my ideals on my family.
And since they're family, I'll lie to them.
I'll deceive them. I'll cause them trouble.
I'll make them worry.
I'll owe them things,
things I'll never be able to repay.
However, I think that's okay.
Kagenui-san...
Miss Good Guy.
If you say that being an impostor is evil,
then I will shoulder the burden of that evil.
If lying is evil,
then I'm fine with being evil.
I don't need them to like me.
I'm fine with being the worst kind of person.
Onii-chan!
As long as she calls me that,
it's enough for me.
The theory of fundamental evil?
As a high school student, ye've learned the theory of fundamental good, right?
It was a concept developed by Chinese philosopher Mencius.
He said that humans are born fundamentally good.
That's the one.
Um...
If the theory of fundamental good is an ideal,
the theory of fundamental evil is the realistic one.
Desire lies at the core of human nature.
And humans are ruled by these desires.
That was the less tactful theory of Xun Zi.
He claimed that humans are born evil.
Born
evil?
Aye.
Thus, if a person does good things,
that is not their true self, but rather, a lie.
That was his theory.
Good is living a lie, being an impostor,
and due only tae fake altruism.
Fake altruism.
False. And thus, by definition, deliberate.
He said that being good is always fake, and therefore,
it constitutes a deliberate intention tae be good.
There was a thought experiment that Kaiki-kun often used tae discuss...
Given the real thing, and an indistinguishable impostor,
which is worth more?
The real thing and an impostor...
Naturally, my response was that the real thing was worth more.
Oshino-kun asserted that they had equal value, though.
But Kaiki-kun's argument was that
the impostor is of far greater value.
In its deliberate attempt tae be the real thing,
it's more real than the real thing.
Kaiki-kun's such a petty villain,
but he does say some neat things.
I suppose ye could say that's the lesson for us here.
It took us ten years tae learn, though.
We're leaving.
We lose.
U-Um, Kagenui-san?
I'm bored.
We're leaving.
I cannae fight when I'm feeling strange like this.
Unlimited Rulebook.
Ye can shoot a bird, but not one that's nesting.
Unlimited Rulebook
A rulebook mostly filled with exceptions.
We'll just say yer little sister is an exception to our justice.
In a way, you're her mentor, so keep a close watch over her.
Anyway, ye weren't ever really serious about fighting us, were ye?
We weren't serious?
I never sensed a desire tae kill.
I don't think ye were holding back,
but tae be honest, it wasn't much fun for me.
If you didn't think I wanted to kill you,
that's because you treated me like a human being, Kagenui-san.
You said we both had a human and an oddity, right?
Since I became this way,
only Oshino's referred to me as a human being.
So I'm the one who wasn't really into it.
I felt weird. I didn't really want to fight.
It was just like facing the old guy in the Hawaiian shirt.
I suppose I've ended up acting like Oshino-kun here.
I kinda regret it...
Pathetic.
So I guess I'll end this
with something Oshino-kun would never say.
Goodbye.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
I was worried you were going to kiss me again,
but I guess you weren't.
Good morning. Welcome home.
Where were you?
Actually, I just went out and fought a human like a monster,
and a monster like a human, all for you.
That was kind of you. Thanks.
Don't overdo it.
Just let me. I do it because I want to.
I know, I know.
You love us.
Don't take it like that.
I hate you both.
Once summer break ends,
I'll introduce you to my girlfriend.
What, Onii-chan?
You have a girlfriend?
Yeah, ever since May.
I'm platinum mad!
Don't tell her anything she doesn't need to know.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
I got way more involved than usual,
Black
Unnumbered Cut
but there was no point in staying there forever.
For now, I'll go back to my room and change.
It's gotten quite late while I was doing all this.
It's time for this monster to bow out.
Tsuhiki Phoenix
Phoenix
Nisemonogatari
End