I'm right!
Karen-chan...
For now, just tell me what happened.
Weren't you going to have a heroic tale for me?
I'll ask once more, my bigger little sister...
Tell me what happened.
Nope!
Araragi-kun?
Araragi-kun, you were really upset when my father hit me, right?
So why are you about to hit Karen-chan?
I do think physical punishment is appropriate in some circumstances.
If you can give some reason that will satisfy Karen-chan, even after you've hit her,
then it's all right.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing to me?
My bad.
I got too emotional.
Hey, Tsubasa-san,
don't be mad at my brother.
This one was my fault.
And if he hit me, I would've hit him back.
I see.
Then I guess I didn't need to interfere.
That's right, Tsubasa-san.
I don't think you would've been able to hit him back, though.
Then I would've bitten him.
You don't know how strong my teeth are.
Onii-chan, don't be mad, okay?
We've been having Hanekawa-san help us with all this.
How can I not be mad?!
Araragi-kun, keep it down.
You'll wake up your parents.
And I didn't realize you yelled at your sisters that way.
I'm surprised.
Playing nice
for Hanekawa.
This is really hard!
Playing nice
for Hanekawa.
Hanekawa-san,
don't get mad at our brother.
He's just worried that we're causing trouble for you.
Jeez.
Araragi-kun,
I'm cooperating with Karen-chan and Tsukihi-chan of my own accord,
so don't blame them.
The Araragi-kun I know wouldn't get angry with his sisters without reason, would he?
Okay, okay.
I won't get mad. I promise.
And you won't tell Mom and Dad?
I won't.
So explain. What happened? What's going on?
Hmm, what happened, I wonder...
Hanekawa, could you come to my room for a second?
Nii-chan is trying to get Tsubasa-san into his room!
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
I'm so
gonna
kill you
All right. Let's go.
It's okay, Karen-chan and Tsukihi-chan.
You did the right thing.
Once he talks to me, I'm sure he'll understand.
I'll tell him everything, so don't worry.
Tsubasa-san!                          Hanekawa-san!
I trust your brother.
Hey, big one.
What is it, little one?
You probably are right.
You always are.
I won't deny that.
But that's all you are.
You're never strong.
And if you're not strong, you'll lose.
You do enough martial arts to know that.
The first requirement of being a hero isn't being right,
it's being strong.
That's why the hero always wins.
You need to learn that.
Until you do, what you're doing is just a game.
And you'll only ever be impostors.
This morning when I woke up, I remembered
It was time to continue the dream I'd forgotten about again
This is fate, I can't just let it be
What's the reason,
you ask?
h
It's because I'm a hero!
Burning up from these flames
The answer that is forged
Is that you've gotta be noble, righteous, and cool!
Hand in hand, lets get going
We'll run faster than we can think!
If I'm with you, I can go anywhere
However, whenever, forever!
When it comes to comparing the Araragi sisters—the Fire Sisters—it's undeniable that Karen, who does the fighting, attracts more attention.
However, that gives the false impression that Tsukihi is the good little sister, and I want to avoid that.
Back in the days when Karen and Tsukihi and I were in elementary school, I recall that Karen got into some kind of trouble.
They weren't called the Fire Sisters back then, and they often acted separately.
In any case, something happened, and Karen got cornered.
Tsukihi jumped off the roof of the school without hesitation to save her.
I don't know if it was luck or if she'd calculated it precisely, but she landed on the roof of a truck that was parked there by chance.
(What is this, a kung-fu movie?)
She survived, but her image as a mature, introverted person was ruined in a flash.
(Of course, she broke several bones, and still has the scars from her "honor wounds", as she prefers to call them)
I was really surprised when she didn't lose a single friend due to that.
Anyway.
Tsukihi is extreme, and she's capable of suppressing that extremity without being aware of it.
This means that whenever she throws a fit, it isn't simply histrionics, but her running wild intentionally.
She runs wild intentionally.
Is something so dangerous even possible?
The problem, then, lies not in her throwing fits, but in the true wildness lying behind them.
That is the essence of who she truly is.
Karen Bee
Part Four
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Four
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Four
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Four
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Four
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Four
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Four
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
It's kind of different.
The way you worry about your sisters is totally different
from how you worry about Senjougahara-san, or Mayoi-chan, or Kanbaru-san, or Sengoku-chan, or me.
Reference
I don't know how to explain it.
It feels more desperate.
Desperate?
It's like you have a totally different personality when you deal with them.
You were pretty hard on them back there, weren't you?
"You're only right, you aren't strong."
It sounded like you were telling yourself that, too.
You're saying they bother me because I have the same problem?
I'm sure it's not what you want to hear.
But I think it's more like you bother yourself.
Hanekawa, you've only known them for a month or so,
so you might not understand.
But I've lived with Karen-chan for fifteen years,
and Tsukihi-chan for fourteen.
And from that experience, I can tell you...
Hanekawa?
Sorry, sorry.
But you still refer to them like they're little kids, eh?
Big mistake!
Don't worry about it.
I call them "Karen-chan" and "Tsukihi-chan," too.
I-It isn't like that.
I was just, y'know, imitating how you talk...
That's right. It's a type of rhetorical trick, and normally, I don't...
Th-That aside...
Let's get to the point, Hanekawa.
We might not have much time.
That's true.
Well, I think I already know how this all started.
They were looking for the source of the charm that's circulating among the middle school kids.
Huh? How did you know?
Sengoku told me, actually.
Unfortunately, my little sisters—
Karen-chan and Tsukihi-chan!
My little sis—
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Karen-chan and Tsukihi-chan are famous among middle school kids.
So Sengoku hears about anything they're up to.
I see.
Come to think of it, wasn't Sengoku-chan one of that charm's victims?
Wait, wasn't she the only one?
Not the only one, no,
but the greatest one.
Nisemonogatari, Book 1
Chapter Six
Karen Bee
"Just sit down on the bed."
"Araragi, you shouldn't just tell girls
But the charms are having a lot of negative effects.
to sit on your bed like that."
"Huh? Why not?"
Chapter Six
Karen Bee
Sengoku told me to sit on the bed as well.
To be exact, she told me I couldn't sit anywhere else.
I remember, and sit down in my chair.
"By the way, Hanekawa, why are you wearing your uniform
this late at night?
Chapter Six
Karen Bee
Right. I wanted to comment on it,
but I couldn't find the chance.
Chapter Six
Karen Bee
Hanekawa Tsubasa is always in her uniform.
"I'm used to you wearing your uniform during summer break,
Negative effects?
Chapter Six
Karen Bee
so it's fine, but... Don't you have any other clothes?
I've never seen you wearing anything else!"
Mostly in terms of relationships.
Chapter Six
Karen Bee
"Haven't you seen me in my pajamas?"
"Pajamas don't count."
To be honest, I've also seen her in her underwear,
but then again, that doesn't count either. I'd rather see
what kind of outfit Hanekawa would pick for going out somewhere!
But when we looked into it, we found that all the charms going around were curses,
When can I see that?
"Well, it was just by chance, but I met with Karen this evening,
Chapter Six
Karen Bee
and then came here. Should I start the story from there?"
Chapter Six
Karen Bee
"Yeah, please."
Nisemonogatari 1
Chapter
Six
Karen Bee
"Yeah, please."
and that at some point, something had changed about them.
Their guess that someone was deliberately spreading them
was probably just a guess.
But even so, it wasn't completely wrong.
By the way,
how long have you been hanging out with them?
I haven't been hanging out with them.
Once in a while, they ask me for help, and I help.
To answer the question of how long it's been...
Hmm...
Since the start of summer vacation, I suppose.
So you helped them.
In other words, you found out who was behind it.
Basically, it was none other than Hanekawa Tsubasa
who was calling Karen's phone all that time.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
I'd prefer it if you didn't try and act like this is my fault.
That's why Oshino was worried about you.
You're too smart, and you'll always find the answer.
I suppose so.
But that doesn't mean I can't do my best.
Yeah.
Just as Karen-chan, Tsukihi-chan, and I...
Just as Karen-chan, Tsukihi-chan, and I must accept our weakness,
you must accept your strength.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
So then what? Karen-chan went to talk to whoever was behind this,
Black
Unnumbered Cut
and they did something to her?
That's right.
I was busy with something else, and only arrived later,
so I didn't see the culprit directly.
If only I could have met up with Karen-chan earlier,
I'd have been able to help.
Karen-chan said who it was, right?
Um...
Some weird, ill-omened guy named Kaiki Deishuu.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
I decided to leave my sisters in Hanekawa's care and take a bath.
To be honest, I needed time to cool off,
or I was just going to yell at them again.
By the way, Hanekawa...
What were you talking about on the phone? With Senjougahara?
Oh, that?
Tsukihi-chan sent a message on her cell phone.
But she said it was strange that there was no response.
So I decided to call.
Despite everything they might say about you, they do trust you.
Okay, well, I figured that was what happened.
But how did you manage to persuade Senjougahara?
It was nothing, really. When I heard her voice,
I guessed most of what was happening.
So I just made a small request.
A small request?
"If you won't be a good girl,
I'll ask Araragi-kun to be my boyfriend."
Scary...
Um...
Since you've seen me naked now,
I suppose that means you'll have to marry me too.
My master.
Shinobu!
What's wrong with you?
You look like a pigeon that's been hit by a peashooter.
Or a vampire that's been hit by a silver bullet, perhaps.
Is it that rare for me to talk?
Or maybe you thought I'd forgotten how?
Shinobu,
y-you...
I got bored.
I'm normally quite talkative.
You know that.
I'm not going to keep my mouth shut forever.
You should understand that, my master.
Thank you.
What are you talking about?
Oh... Um...
These!
These chains...
Weren't you the one who cut them?
Was I?
I really don't remember.
But those arms look pretty stupid.
Let's see.
No need to thank me.
I just do as I please.
I always have, and I always will.
And this time, purely by chance—
and I assure you it was just chance—
your wishes and mine coincided,
my master.
Shinobu, hey...
Hair.
My hair.
Wh-What about your hair?
Wash my hair.
I feel like trying this shampoo stuff, for fun.
From your shadow, I've seen you do it,
and I always thought it looked fun.
Can I touch you?
How would you wash my hair without touching me?
Okay, I'll give you some conditioner, too.
Hey...
Stop.
Don't say a word.
You won't forgive me,
and I'll never forgive you.
And that's fine.
Neither of us forgives the other.
That's fine.
We can't let the past merely be water under the bridge.
Even so, there's no reason that we can't come together.
That's the conclusion I've come to,
after thinking for these past three or four months.
What do you think, my master?
I'm surprised to hear that you were thinking that.
You've been thinking for yourself, haven't you?
I've been in your shadow lately,
so I know.
I can't be sullen forever.
I'm not as petty as that.
And it seems you'll never get this unless I tell you directly.
I do like Pon de Ring.
However...
Golden chocolate is my favorite!
So if you're going to buy two, buy those.
Got it.
A flame wreathe bee.
A supernatural variant of the Asian giant hornet.
Wait, you mean that's—
It's the oddity that's afflicting your colossal sister.
Bigger sister. Not colossal.
Just so we're clear, this isn't my knowledge.
It's that kid's.
Can you understand how I felt?
That sleazy little brat spent every hour of every day filling my head with useless stories of ghosts and monsters.
And I had to sit there and listen without saying a word!
That's horrible!
Black
Unnumbered Cut
And this is one of the stories he told me.
The flame wreathe bee.
I think
it dates back to around the fourteenth or fifteenth century.
A type of infectious disease with no known cause.
The disease starts with a fever so high that it renders its victims unable to move,
proceeding until their death.
In the end, hundreds of people died.
A long time passed before it was stopped by a famous exorcist.
Supposedly, this was written in some scroll or another.
"They were stung by a bee that could not be touched,
and their bodies were wreathed in flames," it said.
Karen is the type who hates to show weakness.
And I'll be honest when I say I didn't notice a thing.
But she was under considerable stress.
She was running a bad fever.
Hanekawa said she felt like she was covered in flames.
In short, she was really sick.
Jeez...
So that's why Hanekawa was covering for her.
I still think it's her own fault.
Her own fault?
You're really tough on your family.
Well, I've been watching for a long time,
so I can't say this surprises me.
But even so, while I'm not certain I agree with your former class president,
I really am surprised.
Former class president?
She's still
class president,
you know.
I don't think I'm being harsh.
But either way, I guess this Kaiki guy
used an oddity to poison my sister.
I don't know if that's possible, but...
It's possible.
Doable, certainly.
But...
If we believe what that tsundere girl told you,
Kaiki was an impostor and a con man.
That's true...
Of course, there's no reason an impostor can't do what the real thing would.
And it's possible for an impostor to seem more real than the real thing.
True...
Certainly, it's possible for someone to be unskilled as a specialist, but still a master con artist.
Unskilled as a specialist...
Black
Unnumbered Cut
But in that case,
they'd be an even bigger problem than someone who was good at it.
Anyone who would bend the supernatural to their will without
the proper talents isn't doing what a normal person would.
Their lack of skill isn't the issue.
They're not even human.
It would be more accurate to say
that they themselves are like an oddity.
Well, I can ask Senjougahara about that.
In fact, I don't have a choice.
The problem is how to get that idiot's—
I guess there's no point in faking this in front of you.
Karen-chan...
How do we get Karen-chan's symptoms down?
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Shinobu, could you eat her disease?
Unfortunately...
The disease is merely the result.
I could make a tasty snack of the bee,
but I can't eat the result of a bee sting.
That's right.
Hmm...
Then what do we do?
Did Oshino say anything about dealing with a flame wreathe bee?
Did he?
I think he might have,
but his lectures tended to wander all over the place.
Come to think of it, it's been a long time since I last had a bath.
Has it?
Yup.
Maybe four hundred years.
A scale beyond my power to imitate.
What are you staring at?
If you're staring this closely at a young girl's naked body,
does that make you a true pervert?
No, that's not what I...
Your passionate gaze is stimulating my imagination a little bit.
Nothing exciting.
For example,
what do you think would happen if I started to scream so loudly
that the whole house could hear?
Just...
stuff like that.
Of course, if you were to offer me a giant pile of donuts to keep my mouth shut,
I would be willing to negotiate.
Go ahead and try.
You and I are one.
Since you can't leave my shadow,
it'll be bad for you, too.
If nothing else, you'll never get any more Mister Donuts.
I see. So that's your answer.
I guess you've grown up a little, my master.
Onii-chan, how long will you be taking that bath?
You were going to listen to my story next, right?
Umm...
Huh?
Onii-chan, where's that girl?
Girl?
What are you talking about?
Don't say nonsensical things during an emergency.
Stupid girl...
Maybe I imagined it.
Definitely!
There was no girl with golden hair,
pale white skin, and a flat chest,
who spoke in a haughty, old-style voice yet appeared to be around eight years old.
You imagined it.
Really?
Well, whatever.
I'll let it slide.
Anyway, Onii-chan, your bath's taking quite a while.
How long will you be?
I'll be out in a second.
Wait in the living room.
'Kay.
And learn to knock.
You've never said that before!
Since when did you stop being a kid?!
Don't get cocky just because you have some muscle now!
Black
Unnumbered Cut
That was scary.
You have a very violent sister.
Shut up.
By the way, I'm sure this isn't something the kid mentioned...
In fact, he deliberately kept it secret.
But when do you suppose you're going to die?
What does that mean?
Well, you know...
You're mostly human,
but at the same time, you're still part vampire.
What does that mean for your lifespan?
Your toughness may have reverted to human levels.
But it's possible that your lifespan remains that of a vampire.
You've retained some of your healing ability, after all.
It's possible you'll live, never mind four hundred,
but five hundred years or more, like me.
And your lover,
your friends,
your underclassman,
your little sisters...
All of them are going to die and disappear.
And in the end, it will just be you and me.
No matter what bonds you forge with others,
time will tear them apart.
Well?
Doesn't thinking about it make you sick?
So here's a plan...
Why don't you kill me,
and go back to being a human for real?
Don't be silly.
It's just like you said.
I won't forgive you,
and you won't forgive me.
That's all there is to it.
And we're done discussing this.
There's nothing left to say.
We live until we die.
Very well, then.
Pray I don't kill you in your sleep,
my master.
Regardless, my life is well past its prime.
I'll while away some of my remaining time
beside you, as your shadow.
But I've no intention of getting along.
Lower your guard, and I'll kill you, then and there.
And so, despite all that was still unforgiven,
we came to a reconciliation as if it was the most inevitable thing in the world.
I can see you checking out that girl in the school uniform
You're making it obvious as hell
I mean come on, I'm standing right here
What do you even think you're doing?
Don't think that I'm going to be here by your side forever
We know that one day,
Someone, somewhere is going to take me
And then I'll be gone, do you understand that?
And when that time comes it'll be too late
Even if you cry, it won't be my problem
And making that face won't get you anywhere
Really, you're easy
And I can't help getting irritated, you know?
Preview
Script: Nisio Isin
Illustrations: Haritama Hiroki
I'm Hanekawa Tsubasa.
We're the fire sisters!
When electronic dictionaries were first being used,
all you could look up was the exact word you were interested in and nothing else.
With a printed dictionary, you can also read the definitions of similar words next to it.
Hello!
Who might
you be?
I used to hear that a lot, but nowadays electronic dictionaries have started having links,
I only know what I know!
Huh?
Hanekawa?
so now they offer more opportunities to look up the definitions of similar words than printed ones.
Now they're so widely used that I wouldn't be surprised if I saw Senjougahara-san use one as a weapon.
Are you really her?
She might be a fake!
Uh...
What hasn't changed is that sometimes I get really
enthusiastic and lose myself completely in the dictionary.
I know, we can check her BREASTS!
Hihihi
Come on, strip!
Ack!
Dictionaries have turned electronic,
but I don't suppose we humans can?
Next time! Karen Bee, Part 5!
Next Episode
Karen Bee        Part Five
She's scary when she's mad.
Hang in there, printed dictionaries!