There's something important we need to discuss, my master.
Red
Unnumbered Cut
Well?
Do you have a moment to talk?
Does it have to be now?
Can it wait until I'm done studying?
It's actually a rather dire situation,
one that requires immediate action.
What is it?
Fine, I'm listening.
Master,
according to top secret information I've acquired,
Mister Donut
is having a sale where all donuts are just 100 yen!
If we don't leave immediately, they'll sell out!
Okay, fine.
I'll go get you some before dinner.
I need some fresh air, anyway.
You like golden chocolate, right?
No.
Take me there.
I want to choose for myself!
It's really sunny out.
Will you be okay?
I'll just get a bit sunburned.
I'm not really a normal vampire anymore.
I won't even need sunscreen.
A hat alone should suffice.
Okay, I'll let you know when we're at the store.
Until then, stay in my shadow.
You'd prefer to minimize your time in the sun, right?
Indeed. The sun is my nemesis.
It'll only take half an hour or so.
No falling asleep on me.
Then I will see you soon. Until then.
Come on!
Impostory
Together now!
When I look at the world covered in a sheet of snow
I take a single step forward
The passion in my heart will never change, never wane
Let's dance to its beat
The moon I found that day while riding on your back
looks like a mirror again today, up there in the starlit sky
and glitters with little flashes of light
Some things will change
But some things never change
Though I may be fickle
for the first time, I now know of eternity
and pledge it to you
I'm platinum happy
but I still get platinum sad
and shed platinum tears
Why? Just why?
Discothèque
"Hmm," Tsukihi nodded as if she didn't really get it at all.
The way she tilted her head looked totally carefree and relaxed.
Droopy eyes, lazy expression. Sloping shoulders, rounded back.
She looks like a sleepy panda. But I mustn't be fooled by her looks.
As clearly obvious from the fact that just this morning she almost turned Karen and me into pincushions,
Araragi Tsukihi is nothing even close to carefree or relaxed.
She's not sleepy at all. She's a wide awake panda. A bear.
If you asked me for my opinion frankly, Karen is easier to tame, because she's a reckless fool.
Tsukihi is a meandering fool, something that's way beyond my control.
If Karen is a red flame, Tsukihi is a blue flame. If you're careless, you'll get burnt.
And not just the skin—roasted to the bone.
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Three
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Three
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Three
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Three
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Three
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Three
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Three
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Onii-chan?
Heading out again?
Yeah... I am.
Will Karen-chan be home late again today, Onii-chan?
I dunno.
I see.
Well, when she gets really into something,
she completely ignores everything else around her.
Why? Did you have something to talk to her about?
Weren't you done with all the
Fire Sisters stuff from the other day?
Yeah, it's nothing, really...
But y'know, well,
it feels like we've been working separately a lot lately.
I'm sure you already noticed,
but I'm not into the whole justice thing as much as she can be.
I like justice—I love justice, even—
but I don't really have any clear image of what it means to me.
You know how Karen-chan says, "My blood of justice won't forgive you!" and such?
And "My blood of justice burns!"
I do, yeah.
I've never felt that way before.
She has justice inside her, and I just don't.
The justice I believe in is Karen-chan's justice. And yours too, actually.
If she wasn't so sure about it,
I don't think I'd believe in something as vague as justice.
In that sense, you're right.
My justice is fake.
I'm too easily influenced by the people around me to claim to be justice.
While Karen-chan fights for justice for the sake of others,
I fight for justice because of the influence of others.
From the very beginning, there's always been that difference between us.
And because of that, Onii-chan...
Lately, I've started thinking that it's time to put the Fire Sisters to bed.
Sounds good to me.
Actually, I think you two have gotten along almost too well up 'til now.
I know it's probably outside my control,
but once she reaches high school, will she bully me like you do?
Don't talk about me like that!
I consider myself to be a helpful, reliable older brother.
Helpful?
You mean like brushing our teeth while grabbing our tits?
Okay, I got it!
Once Karen-chan gets back, we'll discuss the future of the Fire Sisters!
What? So you might split up?
It could happen.
We have creative differences!
If she wants to do it alone, I won't stop her.
I'll hold back my tears as we part ways!
Come to our farewell party, okay?
I'll invite lots of middle school girls and stuff.
Fine, I'll make sure I have a free schedule.
So, my helpful brother, weren't you on your way out?
Oh, that's right.
Watch the house, okay?
I'll be home soon.
Need me to pick anything up?
Nope. Have funs.
Funs I shall have.
And go back to your room.
I can't open the door with you here dressed like that.
I'm saying, stop wandering around half naked.
Don't dress like that.
Hey, Tsukihi-chan...
I'm gonna take it off.
Wh-What?
Stop it, Onii-chan... What are you doing?
No!
Black
Unnumbered Cut
I knew it.
What? What? What?
What's going on?
Why is my brother stripping off my clothes,
binding my hands, and holding me down?
Um, Tsukihi-chan...
Didn't you have a scar here?
The scar that should have been there is gone.
The doctors were certain that the scar would never, ever fade, but...
Wait. There aren't any scars on your body whatsoever.
Scars heal. I'm a human being!
Yeah, I guess so.
And get off me already, Onii-chan!
If you just wanted to see if the scar was there, you didn't have to grab my hands and pin me down!
That's... That's true.
Why did you grab my breast before getting off me?
Just because.
I was wondering how it felt. It was right in front of me.
That's the only reason?!
Yeah, see...
Squish squish squish squish.
Don't touch it with your feet!
And don't make such weird sound effects!
Jeez, Onii-chan, you're touching your little sisters' boobs way too much!
Um, if someone took that out of context they'd get some really strange ideas about me.
Jeez...
Jeez, jeez, jeez!
Why is it that sisters have pure relationships with their boyfriends,
but are still required to have a physical relationship with their brother?
Oh...
What was his name?
Your boyfriend.
Rosokuzawa-kun?
You haven't split up yet?
Sorry, but I'm in love.
Karen-chan and her boyfriend, Mizudori-kun, haven't been getting along very well.
But they'll be all right, I think.
Okay, I'm leaving now.
Don't bother coming back!
You're not welcome in this home anymore!
Oh, but I will always return... to your heart!
Flocky chou?
What magic is this? Such a thing is possible?
Combining the Pon de Ring and the French Cruller...
It's incredibly amazing!
Old-fashioned!
Just looking at it reveals how delicious it must be.
I can tell! I don't even have to eat it.
I will, though!
And the tofu donut's name alone is so enticing...
And look at these muffins, lined up like jewels.
Why was the existence of these muffins hidden from me?
Curse them! I won't forgive them.
However, and there's no need to even say this, but having all the wonderful donuts I've consumed so far,
including the golden chocolate,
all laid out before me in such numbers is the best part!
Simply wonderful!
Master, can I eat all of them?
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Of course not!
What, then?!
You're forcing me to select only a few to eat
from the dozens upon dozens set out here?
I'll bring you once a month or something.
Exercise some restraint for today.
Let's just see what you can handle and start with maybe three.
Oh, my master...
Don't be so foolish.
If you're thinking about the future,
then why not consider this an investment for getting on my good side?
And what good would that do me?
Ahh, enough. Fine.
How about this.
We'll each choose five.
Ten total.
And we can share.
But no muffins and no pies.
They aren't part of the 100-yen sale.
Very well.
I can handle that.
So, Shinobu...
I wanted to ask you something.
On my way to Kanbaru's place, and on my way back,
those two girls who asked me for directions...
The Kyoto accent woman and the "posed look" girl.
What did you think of them?
I suppose I could tell you about the one with the posed look.
What do you mean?
She wasn't human. She was an oddity.
She took a human form,
Ononoki                       Yotsugi
but like me, she isn't the age she appears to be.
And naturally, I'd imagine that Ononoki Yotsugi is an alias.
I was wondering about her first name, Yotsugi.
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Her first name sounds just like that Kagenui woman.
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
Kage
nui
Yoz
uru
nui
She's probably using the name to bind her,
much like I'm bound by that brat in the Hawaiian shirt.
Oshino                 Meme
Oshino          Shinobu
Basically, Ononoki Yotsugi is Kagenui Yozuru's familiar.
A familiar?
That's what you'd call it in your culture.
A shikigami, perhaps?
So the two of them—
Or Kagenui-san, at least, is a specialist...
I've no intention of sharing information about proper humans.
And I don't really want you to see me as a useful tool anyway.
I am not such a cheap woman that a few donuts would loosen my lips.
I'm neither your familiar nor your shikigami.
If you really insist on knowing,
why not ask the man sitting in the seat right over there?
Kaiki-san,
after all that grandstanding when you left,
why are you here, eating donuts?
Some minor business.
Just unpleasant, minor business.
Araragi, it's nothing for you to concern yourself over.
I'll be gone shortly.
I'd prefer if you left now.
Don't be in such a hurry.
I didn't ever want to see you again, either.
Because of you, I lost a lot of money.
You do know Kagenui Yozuru and Ononoki Yotsugi, right?
You want to know about them?
I'll tell you. Pay up.
Fine.
How much do I need to pay
for you to tell me?
Let me see.
That will do.
Araragi.
I'll allow you to pay with this meager change, as a gift to honor your relationship with Senjougahara.
Now tell me about Kagenui Yozuru and Ononoki Yotsugi!
They are specialists.
Ghost busters, like me.
Of course, while I'm an impostor, they're the real thing.
I'm a con man, and they are exorcists.
Exorcists?
I said "they" out of habit.
To be precise, though, Kagenui is the exorcist, and Ononoki is her familiar.
So you know them?
What makes you think so?
Just the way you talk...
The way you speak implies that you do.
I merely know their names.
Kagenui is rather famous in the business.
Kagenui Yozuru and Ononoki Yotsugi
are modern-day exorcists.
But Araragi, even as specialists go,
they specialize in a very limited field.
That two-man cell specializes
in immortal creatures.
Exorcists specializing in immortal oddities?
Jeez...
Then they're probably after us.
You think we're their targets?
That may not necessarily be the case, my master.
I've eaten many immortal creatures.
I kill the immortal, too.
Timed Light
One
It's odd to call oddities "immortal" in the first place. We aren't even alive.
Three
Yeah.
Well, I guess if you're not living, you can't die.
So I guess oddities are immortal by default.
But strict definitions aside,
when you say that they might not be after us, Shinobu,
does that mean there may be vampires besides us in this city?
They wouldn't have to be vampires, but yes.
It wouldn't be strange.
No. I suppose it would.
Come to think of it, even just among my acquaintances,
you can find plenty of people who have an oddity inside them.
Like Kanbaru Suruga, with a monkey in her left hand.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Or Hanekawa Tsubasa, with a cat inside her mind.
So it wouldn't be particularly odd if there were others who housed creatures that I don't know about.
Kagenui-san and Ononoki-chan.
If they're setting up base in the same abandoned building as Oshino,
they're likely in the same business.
I should deal with them quickly.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Ye again?
Hello.
First, I should thank ye.
I followed the directions ye gave,
and they led me to the Eikou Cram School.
And ye really ended up telling Yotsugi, as well.
Um, I'm sorry...
I'd like to make something clear.
You came to this city to exterminate us, right?
You've come to kill her, an immortal creature not of this world,
along with me, her servant, yes?
Both of you asking me for directions was no coincidence.
You were investigating me.
Devil kid,
it seems like ye misunderstood.
Matters pertaining tae the iron-blooded, hot-blooded, cold-blooded vampire,
king and slayer of oddities,
Kiss-shot Acerola-orion Heart-under-blade,
are considered tae have been resolved.
And our industry hardly has the free time tae squander resources on a normal human
with a few lingering aftereffects.
Of course, that's all thanks tae the habitual interference and meddling of Oshino-kun.
Oshino-kun?
Did she just say "Oshino-kun"?
Hey, Master. Focus.
Yellow
Unnumbered Cut
You have other things to think about right now.
That's right. That's right...
If they aren't here for Oshino Shinobu and Araragi Koyomi,
then why are Kagenui-san and Ononoki-chan here?
Oh, shut up! Shut up, shut up, shut up!
How long will you stand there ringing the doorbell?
Can't you tell I'm pretending to not be here?!
Unlimited Rulebook.
I said, with a posed look.
Calm down, devil kid.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
No need tae get so worked up.
Oshino-kun would probably say something like,
"Yer looking lively. Did something good happen?"
Fuck you!
You...
You bastards...
You killed my sister...
My sister Tsukihi-chan...
You'll pay!
What, that was yer sister?
I see.
Right, yer name is Araragi, too.
Thought it was just a coincidence.
I understand.
Our information had some gaps.
Then that must have been a shock.
Sorry, sorry.
You think an apology will help?
Observe.
H-Huh?
Oni Onii-chan,
you appear to have a thing for immortal creatures.
Your sister is possessed by an immortal bird.
That was never truly your sister.
It is human, yet not human.
What you see there is the rare firebird, the evil phoenix.
I said, with a posed look.
Enough.
I will not allow any more of this.
You can't wish to attract more attention than you already have, correct?
We dinnae care.
We're no' clever enough tae be concerned with time or place.
And how will ye stop us?
What can ye do?
Vampire...
Former vampire.
Without yer skills, you're no threat to me.
That may be!
But whether or not that's true for you, what of her?
I doubt she's strong enough to withstand my energy drain.
And if I drain her dry,
I think I could take you.
She's bluffing!
I'm not going to interfere with you,
but I do request that you withdraw for now.
You could do that for me, couldn't you?
Since time isn't an important factor for you.
Fine, then.
As ye wish. Let's go.
Despite what I said,
we have no interest in killing a sister in front of her brother.
But naturally...
She isn't yer real sister.
Not my real sister...
An impostor?
I'm sure the devil kid needs some time tae gather his thoughts.
We'll give ye time, out of respect for the legendary vampire.
We'll pretend tae fall for your bluff,
so prepare yerself in any way ye'd like.
We'll return tomorrow.
Make sure everything's been handled by then.
Running won't help.
Just so we're clear, neither of us are as easy tae deal with as Oshino-kun.
We cannae let any prey escape.
And if ye try to stop us, we'll ignore the ruling that decided ye were harmless,
and we'll eliminate ye as well.
Goodbye.
Why?
Why are you trying to kill Tsukihi-chan?
There's no reason for you to!
'Course there is.
She's an oddity. A monster.
A monstrous impostor that snuck into a human family,
pretended to be human, and deceived humans!
That's what we'd call "evil."
We're the good guys.
We cannae ignore a con like that.
We won't allow it.
I can see you checking out that girl in the school uniform
You're making it obvious as hell
I mean come on, I'm standing right here
What do you even think you're doing?
Don't think that I'm going to be here by your side forever
We know that one day,
Someone, somewhere is going to take me
And then I'll be gone, do you understand that?
And when that time comes it'll be too late
Even if you cry, it won't be my problem
And making that face won't get you anywhere
Really, you're easy
And I can't help getting irritated, you know?
Preview
Script: Nisio Isin
Illustrations: Haritama Hiroki
It's me, Araragi Koyomi.
We're the fire—
Silent
I don't want you to think I'm complaining,
but don't you think there have been rather too many sequels, prequels, part twos, second seasons,
I saw it on TV!
I want in on the action!
Say that earlier!
reinventions, additional content works, spin-offs, side stories, bonus material works, and revivals as of late?
What the hell is
going on here, fire sisters?
Whoa! Onii-chan!
I mean, I'm a fan myself, so I can't help being happy,
You two
are still fakes!
We're sorry
Huh? Is that the script?
Slipping Out
but it sometimes makes me want to complain that nothing really new is being made
and worry that our culture is on the decline.
A Technicolor Animated Movie
in All Theaters
Kizumonogatari
Production Underway
Starring Araragi Koyomi
That's what I told Sengoku the other day, and this is how she answered:
Don't worry, Koyomi-oniichan.
Our hearts are one!
We're the fire sisters!
This is nothing new.
It's always been like that.
Next time. Tsukihi Phoenix, Part 4.
Next Episode
Tsukihi Phoenix    Part Four
You'll see us again soon!
Naturally, it's the final episode.