My bigger little sister, Araragi Karen.
A third-year in middle school.
She had her birthday at the end of June and turned 15.
She's always been a tomboy who excelled at most sports,
but her talents seem to have been best suited for combat.
She earned her black belt in record time.
She enjoys fighting too much to give off a truly feminine aura.
I wouldn't call her manly,
but the aggressive look in her eye makes her appear boyish.
And the littler little sister, Araragi Tsukihi.
A second-year in middle school,
her birthday falls in early April,
which makes her fourteen now.
Karen is, well,
exactly what she looks like.
Though Tsukihi's appearance belies her true nature,
what's important is that her true nature does not belie her appearance.
She looks extremely feminine,
but she's more ill-tempered than Karen,
and she's more easily provoked.
Her fits could almost be called hysterics.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
The Fire Sisters of Tsuganoki 2nd Middle School...
Black
Unnumbered Cut
The two of them formed something like a rescue squad, or maybe a heroic duo,
Black
Unnumbered Cut
playing a game that occupies the majority of their time.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Of course, were you to tell them that...
It isn't a game, Nii-chan!
We aren't just defenders of justice.
We're justice itself, Onii-chan.
Is what they'd tell you.
I can usually anticipate what they'll say.
But I can say this without hesitation.
Araragi Karen and Araragi Tsukihi,
the Fire Sisters.
Their actions are nothing but a game.
My dearest little sisters.
You two are hopeless impostors.
This morning when I woke up, I remembered
It was time to continue the dream I'd forgotten about again
This is fate, I can't just let it be
What's the reason,
you ask?
h
It's because I'm a hero!
Burning up from these flames
The answer that is forged
Is that you've gotta be noble, righteous, and cool!
Hand in hand, lets get going
We'll run faster than we can think!
If I'm with you, I can go anywhere
However, whenever, forever!
The older of my little sisters.
Araragi Karen.
Ever since elementary school, she has mostly sported a ponytail.
Though one time, around when she entered middle school, I think she dyed her hair...
She made it such a shocking, attention-drawing pink, that not even anime characters could really compete with it.
Her reasons for doing so are a mystery to this day, but the outcome was predictable.
Mother slapped her hard in the face.
(in Mother's defense, that was the one and only time where she ever lost her temper and raised a hand at her children)
That night, Karen dyed her hair back to black (with Indian ink).
However, she kept on trying to live up to her notorious middle school debut, and you can guess how that shaped her personality.
To be blunt, she isn't what you would call "cute".
But she is cool.
Karen has been training in martial arts for a long time, so she has great posture.
Because of that, she seems a good five centimeters taller than she actually is.
That also happens to be one of the reasons she never wears skirts.
"My legs would look too long in one," she says,
as she sets off to school sporting her beloved, messy jersey.
I guess she's the only one who could still look cool wearing something like that.
Karen Bee
Part Two
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Two
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Two
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Two
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Two
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Two
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Two
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Sengoku, that's how you do it at home?
Um...
D-Do what?
Those bangs.
B-Bangs?
Wh-What are you talking about?
She's pretending to have no idea.
I-It's not like I worked up the courage to change my hairstyle
just because you were coming over for the first time, or anything.
Well, come on in, Koyomi-oniichan.
Sure...
Huh?
Sengoku.
Where are your parents?
My parents work on Saturdays as well.
Just like mine.
So that's why you answered the phone.
My room is on the second floor.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Sengoku, that clo—
Don't open it!
—set...
I'd never forgive anyone for opening it, not even you.
Okay, have a seat over there, Koyomi-oniichan.
There? On the bed?
You sure?
Yeah.
You can't sit anywhere but the bed.
This room is kind of hot, isn't it?
Even if you aren't hot, you still have no choice but to take off your hoodie.
Me?
No choice, huh?
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Koyomi-oniichan, let's play the King Game.
Sengoku, do you even know what the King Game is?
It has nothing to do with a deck of cards.
I know what it is.
It's like Simon Says, right?
Simon
Says
The king's word is law!
Too political!
Well, I've never played it before, so I don't really know.
But, Sengoku,
I'm not sure you can play the
King Game with only two players.
Why not?
I'm fine with either role.
Giving the orders and taking them.
W-Well, let's not play that.
Then let's play the Game of Life, Koyomi-oniichan.
The Game of Life, huh?
Sure, that sounds fun.
The word of Life is law!
Deep!
Annals ?
Annals 1
Annals 2
Basho's Poetry
The Tale
of the
Bamboo Cutter
The Tale
of the
Bamboo Cutter
18th Kabuki Collection
5     1
Medieval Novel Anthology 1
Medieval Novel Anthology 2
Modern Haiku Anthology
Modern Japanese Poetry 1
Modern Japanese Poetry 2
Commentary Catalog   2
Commentary Catalog   3
Commentary Catalog   1
The Story of History 1
The Story of History 2
The Story of History 3
The Tale of Genji
The Vale of Tears 1
The Vale of Tears 2
Ueda Akinari's Works 1
Ueda Akinari's Works 2
Anthology of Senryu and Kyoka Poems    1
The Tale of the Heike
Chikamatsu's Puppet Plays 1
Chikamatsu's Puppet Plays 2
Chikamatsu's Puppet Plays 3
Study of Classics 1
Study of Classics 2
Saikaku's Works 1
Saikaku's Works 2
Excerpts from the Tale of Uji 3
Excerpts from the Tale of Uji ?
Story of the Bowman 1
Story of the Bowman 2
Story of the Bowman 3
Ten Thousand Leaves
Furai Sanjin's Works
Anthology of Tales from the Past
Anthology of Tales from
The Pillow Book
An Account of My Hut
Provincial Records
Sanka - Kinkai Anthology
The Chronicles of Japan  1
The Chronicles of Japan  2
The Chronicles of Japan  3
The Vale of Tears 1
The Vale of Tears 2
Kabuki Scripts 1
Kabuki Scripts 2
3       2
Diary of the Writer
Tale of the Hollow Tree
Ancient Poetry
Ghosts & Other Oddities
Elements of Science
1   2
1     2     1     2
Oh, yeah.
Issa's Works
Tale of Sumiyoshi
War of Lands 2
War of Lands 1
The Lotus Sutra    2
The Lotus Sutra    1
Tale of Ise 2
Tale of Ise 1
Tale of Heiji
Tale of Hougen
Sarashina Diary 2
Sarashina Diary 1
Wakefulness at Night
Essays on Poetry                2
Essays on Poetry                1
The Diary of Lady Murasaki    2
The Diary of Lady Murasaki    1
Gikeiki            2
Gikeiki            1
Tale of Heike           2
Tale of Heike           1
The Great Mirror
Prayers from Kojiki  2
Prayers from Kojiki  1
We used to play that at my place, right?
Yeah, I remember.
Yeah?
I never forgot.
Koyomi-oniichan will not get dirty thoughts
from looking at Sengoku's body.
Aren't you glad I'm such a gentleman, Sengoku?
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Time
Passes
Sengoku, has anything odd happened lately?
Wh-What do you mean?
I mean anything like what happened before.
No, I've been fine.
I see.
But there's some weird charm going around, as usual.
At your school?
Yeah, but not just at my school.
Among all the middle schools.
I think Rara-chan and her sister are doing something.
Doing something?
When I talked to her a while ago,
she asked about what happened with the snake.
And since I couldn't tell her the truth,
I didn't say too much.
But she was getting others to help her investigate stuff.
In other words,
it has to do with that charm.
But hey, that whole curse was basically nonsense, right?
In your case, you just chose the wrong way to handle it.
Yeah.
I was the only one who had anything actually happen like it did, I think.
From what I know, anyway.
Then...
But I don't think they're actually worried
about anyone performing the charm at all.
I think they probably don't even believe in the supernatural.
Yeah, I'm sure.
It seems like they're more concerned
with the fact that nonsense of that sort is going around.
They said they're trying to discover who's spreading it.
I doubt someone's trying to spread it.
And even should they find someone, now that it's spread, it isn't his or her responsibility anymore.
That's just like Rara-chan... Or rather, the Fire Sisters.
They seemed like they were hinting
that someone had deliberately spread them with a specific goal.
That does sound just like them...
Sheesh.
I'm gonna have to talk to Karen.
It isn't something I have to get involved in.
But given how much Sengoku Nadeko is involved, it's delicate.
K-Koyomi-oniichan?
It's nothing!
I'm fine, Sengoku.
Anyway, Sengoku...
You look better that way.
I mean your bangs.
You should do it like that outside.
I-It's too embarrassing!
But if you want me to...
I'll do my best.
Yeah, doing your best is always good.
Anyway, we're almost done with the Game of Life.
What do you want to do after this?
Twister!
I don't know what that is.
How do you play it? Show me.
Okay, I'll show you...
I'll show your body.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
I can't wait!
Black
Unnumbered Cut
After that, Sengoku's mom suddenly came home.
I-I didn't tell them you were coming over!
She'll get mad! She'll get mad!
If she sees me dressed this way, she'll think I'm a pervert!
What is this feeling?
I think the fact that there was a problem at her workplace
saved something important for me, as a man.
It was supposed to be tomorrow, but eh.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
This is Kanbaru Suruga!
Kanbaru Suruga...
Primary weapon, accelerator.
You're a cyborg?!
That voice, that retort.
It must be Araragi-senpai.
Yeah, but...
Hey, you're at home, right?
Yes, I am.
Would you wait a minute, Araragi-senpai?
I'll take my clothes off this minute.
Why?!
What are you talking about, Araragi-senpai?
It may be over the phone, but I'm still speaking to you.
Thus, courtesy dictates that I must be naked.
Don't speak as though I've never heard of courtesy.
And stop trying to find excuses to strip!
You've underestimated me.
I guess you don't understand how fast I really am.
I'm already naked!
Already naked?!
Your perversion has really gone further than I'm willing to tolerate, Kanbaru!
Oh, my...
This is my house, and this is my room.
When it comes to what I wear or don't wear,
that's my decision, and no one else's.
You're right. Sorry.
You weren't getting naked outside or anything.
I'm sorry for yelling.
No, so long as you understand, it's fine.
No matter how liberated I feel when naked,
I only occasionally get naked when I'm not at home.
You do it occasionally?!
Like in a bath.
Or with the basketball team.
You won't trick me this time.
I bet it was at the bath during your team trip, right?
Close.
It was on our trip.
During our first year, I led a naked team trip.
I hope your team gets dissolved!
What's wrong, Araragi-senpai?
It was obviously a joke.
For you to believe such an obvious lie,
you might actually be more perverted than I am.
Wh-What?
Black
Unnumbered Cut
What's wrong, Kanbaru?
I accidentally forgot to close the door to my room...
Grandmother
And my grandmother came down the hallway.
She looked at me with sad eyes,
and passed me without a word!
Well, the granddaughter she raised was on the phone, stark naked.
My life is over.
How can I ever talk to her again?
Hey, Kanbaru.
Sorry to interrupt your emotional trauma,
but I unexpectedly have the day off from my test prep.
I know I promised to help clean your room tomorrow,
but how about today?
Sure...
That's fine.
Whichever day is best for you.
Then I'll be right there.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Oh, it's you, Nii-chan?
I thought it was an enemy.
Do you have enemies?
Jeez.
Doing handstands like that in public...
Don't you have any dignity?
You should act more like a girl who's going through puberty.
What if you get a reputation?
I'm not sure I follow,
but I feel like my hypocrisy-detector is going off.
It's doing nothing of the sort.
What are you doing out here?
Community service.
Just a bit of volunteer work.
Volunteer work?
You don't even know what that word means, idiot.
What are you doing, Nii-chan?!
That's dangerous.
What's dangerous is what you're doing.
And what are you doing?
I told you, community service.
Who do you think I am?
I don't know.
Who are you, anyway?
Cutting down a thousand demons...
The Watchdog of Hell, Dekamaster!
How cool...
Super-cool and perfect!
I guarantee that, if nothing else, that pose is not cool at all.
Figures, since I'm burning with passion!
Burn to death.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
But I will admit that I enjoy the inherent humor of saying cool things in that ridiculous pose.
I see, I see...
Then we'll make it a running gag of mine.
Okay, let's practice.
Say something cool. Anything at all.
If you wanna pass, you'll have to get through me!
Cooler than expected.
And the inverse...
Leave this to me. You go on ahead!
Anyways,
I'm busy with some stuff right now.
Nii-chan, if you want to chat,
let's talk tonight when Tsukihi-chan's there too.
Will that work?
Hello?
Oh, yeah...
Nii-chan...
It's okay.
It looks like this really will be over soon.
Seems I'll have a heroic tale to tell tonight!
Who'd listen to that?
The worst part of my day so far
is finding out that you've nearly finished middle school,
but still walk on your hands through the city.
Bye!
Hasta la vista!
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
Suruga's
Grandmother:
Um...
Be kind to Suruga,
Koyomi.
K-Kanbaru?
Is that you, Araragi-senpai?
Wait, Kanbaru!
Do not turn over right now.
If you turn over, we'll have a big problem!
Um...
Oh, I apologize for all this.
I'm embarrassed to let you see the ordinariness of my body.
But for you to open the door without knocking...
That isn't anything like the Araragi-senpai
I know, that paragon of virtue.
Um, well...
I wanted to see you depressed.
If such an ugly thing satisfies you,
you're free to watch as much as you like.
Look long and well.
This is who Kanbaru Suruga truly is.
With nothing at all concealed.
Well, that is...
Sorry.
Sorry, Kanbaru.
Let me take responsibility.
Responsibility?
What could you mean by responsibility, Araragi-senpai?
Let's get married!
Wh-Why marriage?
Well, even if it was just your backside, I saw you naked.
You're skipping a few steps there.
By that logic,
how many girls would you need to marry?
That isn't a very nice thing to say!
Araragi-senpai,
that's an extraordinarily attractive offer,
but you don't need to take responsibility.
If you did that, Senjougahara-senpai would get mad at me.
Instead, Araragi-senpai, I do have a request.
Would you fulfill it?
Sure, anything.
For today, I'm your slave!
I'd like to get dressed. Could you wait in the hall?
No
Entry
Kanbaru, what's this?
Oh, my team uniform.
Come
to
a
Complete
Stop
Naoetsu
I wondered where it had gone.
I guess it was buried over there.
No
Entry
A practice uniform?
No, it's a memento from my first year,
when we made it to nationals.
Take a look at the inside.
All of my teammates signed it.
Do you not understand the concept of treasuring your memories?
My memories are always in my heart.
Great line, but that's not the point!
You know, I don't think I saw you ever play basketball except maybe once.
Hey, Kanbaru.
Would you put this on?
Sure.
Though I've grown out my hair, so I'll look different than I did back then.
Your hair grows crazy fast.
Yeah?
No
Entry
Yeah.
I've heard normal hair grows at a rate of one centimeter per month.
No
Entry
But yours has grown at least five.
Well, I'm really lewd.
She said it frankly!
That's right.
I'm so lewd, I thought that "peperoncini" was a dirty word for years.
You should have realized that when you ate it!
I once misheard "family rate plan" as "family rape plan."
Family
Rape
Family Rape
Dangerous
Object
I mean, I once misheard "family data plan" as "family dating plan."
Dangerous
Object
Family
Dating
That doesn't really make it better!
And I remember recently thinking
"bracelet" meant "let's take a breath."
That isn't erotic at all. It's just a misunderstanding!
ERO
TIC
Instead of "Don't worry,"
I accidentally said "Bracelet" during a match.
Got me really embarrassed.
I'll never forget my teammates' stunned expressions.
Stop it!
That flashback is too embarrassing!
Well, how is it?
Something like this, Araragi-senpai?
Y-Yeah.
When I wear this, I feel the way I did back then.
Back then?
When you played basketball?
No
Entry
No, the naked team trip.
You know exactly what you're doing, don't you?!
Black
Unnumbered Cut
The Glasses-Wearing
Secretary and the
Glasses-Wearing Prince
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
We can throw this one out.
I guess it goes in the flammable trash.
Araragi-senpai, that may be flaming hot,
but it's definitely not trash.
It may be rotten, but I need it.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
But all of these look the same.
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Can you tell the difference when you read them?
Of course.
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Everything looks the same to one who isn't familiar with it.
Naoetsu
Knowledge and education are required to properly judge such a thing.
I see.
But still...
The Glasses-Wearing
Secretary and the
Glasses-Wearing Prince
The Glasses-Wearing
Secretary and the
Glasses-Wearing Prince
The Glasses-Wearing
Secretary and the
Glasses-Wearing Prince
I guess they're all handsome.
Safety          First
I was just thinking you like 'em handsome.
Maybe you aren't really a big pervert.
Don't all girls like handsome guys?
So it's natural to enjoy seeing handsome guys together.
It's basically like an idol group, right?
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
P-Please don't use simplified examples!
It's not as though you only like guys who are overweight
Safety          First
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
Watch
for
Falling
Books
or are turned on by the smell of old men.
U-Um, well...
If you say that to me, there's nothing else I can do...
Watch
for
Falling
Books
I'll strip!
I'll strip right now.
No, no, no, no.
When you think about it, being underdressed at home is actually pretty normal.
And when you're outside, it's only in a bath, right?
I'm sorry for all the things I've said.
I don't want you to apologize!
Araragi-senpai,
listen to what I have to say first!
And as you yourself said on the phone,
maybe I'm the bigger pervert.
Safety          First
Naoetsu
Perfect, she's confused.
It's like you cast a spell.
ONE WAY
That's... No!
I just happened to have a lot of books like that around there!
ONE WAY
There's more hardcore BL below us, in the lower strata!
I know that handsome guys isn't all there is to BL!
WORK AREA IS OFF LIMITS FOR UNAUTHORIZED PERSONNEL
Keep looking!
ONE WAY
Come on, Kanbaru.
Stop
If you actually have to look for it,
it isn't really something you...
Stop
I guess it's time for me to prove my innocence with deeds, not words.
Araragi-senpai, prepare yourself!
For what?!
Don't worry.
It only hurts at first.
It'll feel good soon.
You have a pretty nice body yourself.
I like these muscles.
They feel great to touch!
Stop struggling!
It makes it harder to get your pants off!
That was when I swore
that no matter when or how I encountered Hachikuji,
I would never open the conversation
Watch out for falling objects
with sexual harassment.
I can see you checking out that girl in the school uniform
You're making it obvious as hell
I mean come on, I'm standing right here
What do you even think you're doing?
Don't think that I'm going to be here by your side forever
We know that one day,
Someone, somewhere is going to take me
And then I'll be gone, do you understand that?
And when that time comes it'll be too late
Even if you cry, it won't be my problem
And making that face won't get you anywhere
Really, you're easy
And I can't help getting irritated, you know?
Script: Nisio Isin
Illustrations: Haritama Hiroki
Preview
This is Senjougahara Hitagi-sama.
Everyone loved the first episode! We're the Fire Sisters!
They say that lying is the first step towards stealing,
but doesn't that make it seem like lying is the lesser sin?
Let's do up your hair! We're finally the protagonists!
But fraud is often more damaging than theft, isn't it?
What?! Do
you want to
cut it,
Senjougahara?
Um...
I dunno...
Wouldn't stealing be the first step towards lying?
Okay,
go ahead
A haiku. Robbed from and plundered. My heart,
loosed from my body. Defrauded and scammed.
Is she gonna
be okay?
Next time: Karen Bee, Part 3.
Next Episode
Karen Bee       Part Three
I'm going to murder Araragi Koyomi.
Ahhhh!
Get me
a mirror.