Where's the big one?
Hanekawa-san's looking after her.
Then give me the details.
Sure, okay.
But will you promise me something first?
Are you in a position to make demands?
Sure, I am. I'm your little sister.
And I'm your big brother, so I can refuse them.
Fine. Forget it.
By the way, what were you going to ask me to do?
Not to get mad at Karen-chan.
No.
You can be mad at me,
but don't get mad at Karen-chan.
I'm getting mad at both of you.
You can be mad at Karen-chan,
but please don't get mad at me.
I'm already mad! So start talking and get it off your chest!
You think you're so cool.
You promised you wouldn't get mad when Hanekawa-san was around.
Do you have any regrets, Onii-chan?
Regrets?
Of course I do.
Who doesn't?
Well, I don't know.
I guess I'm not the type to regret things.
I bet.
You two are like that.
But it means that sometimes,
I'll regret that I didn't regret something I should have.
Not that it matters.
I guess you really want a strangling.
No, that's not it...
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Then get to the point.
I know, Onii-chan! I'll tell you something cool.
Something cool?
You know how I always say I'm "platinum" mad?
It was originally "piddling" mad.
So it doesn't actually mean I'm as mad as the word "platinum" would make you think.
I've never heard you say "platinum" mad.
How come you don't know?!
I'm platinum mad!
You're clearly extremely upset!
And stop trying to cleverly change the subject.
Okay, Onii-chan.
Then why don't you tell me something you regret?
I want to hear it.
Just telling you straight out would be kind of upsetting.
So maybe we could, like, share secrets?
Like we were on a school trip or something!
Idiot...
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Still, what I regret, huh?
It's hard to come up with something now that I think about it.
Like, something that's kind of embarrassing.
Like... Oh...
Why don't you have any friends?
I have friends now!
Do you?
How many?
How many, you ask?
Listen, and be amazed!
Five!
Wow, how amazing.
Poor Onii-chan...
You're going to die of loneliness!
Don't be so mean to your brother!
Anyway, I have some now,
but you're asking why I didn't have any for a while?
Well, here's what I used to think.
If you make friends, that means you become less—
No, I've already heard enough embarrassing stuff.
I'm sorry I asked.
Don't apologize yet!
I haven't said anything embarrassing!
Stop it, Onii-chan! That's enough!
You needn't reopen the wounds anymore!
Stop it... It's over!
It's not over!
Araragi-kun, I can hear you from upstairs!
And I can hear you talking about something that really doesn't sound too important.
Could you be a little quieter?
Yeah, sorry.
I'll be more care—
A
Karen Bee
Part Five
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
A
This morning when I woke up, I remembered
It was time to continue the dream I'd forgotten about again
This is fate, I can't just let it be
What's the reason,
you ask?
h
It's because I'm a hero!
Burning up from these flames
The answer that is forged
Is that you've gotta be noble, righteous, and cool!
Hand in hand, lets get going
We'll run faster than we can think!
If I'm with you, I can go anywhere
However, whenever, forever!
Let's talk about Araragi Karen for a while.
Of course, this is just the version of events I heard from Hanekawa and Tsukihi.
So it may differ slightly from what happened.
Cancel
playback
Replay
By title
o=o
By artist
New songs
o=o
Genre
Duet
o=o
Back then
Raw playback
o=o
Guide vocal
Artist's video
o=o
Welcome, young lady.
My name is Kaiki.
kaicho - a written masterpiece
kaichou - 1) exhibit a Buddhist image (by opening the doors of the sanctuary) 2) hold a gambling party
kaichou - 1) harmony 2) (a) harmony; (a) melody
gaichou - a harmful bird
kaichin - state, express
kaitsuu - open for traffic
kaidzuka - a shell mound; a kitchen midden
kaitsuke - buying; purchasing
kaitsuburi - a little grebe; a dabchick
kaitsumamu - sum up; summarize
kaite - buyer
kaitei - a revision
kaiteki - comfortable
kaitetsu - shingled iron
"Kai," like a mound of clamshells. "Ki," like a dead tree.
kare-eda: a withered (dead) branch
kare-obana: withered eulalia grass (appears in Basho's works among others)
kare-gashi: phrase used for persons who need not be named
kare-gata: the time of separation in a relationship
kare-gare: the withering of plants
kare-ki: a dead (withered) tree
* ni hana: if wishes were horses,
* mo yama no nigiwai: anything is better than nothing
ga-reki: debris; rubble
gareki-gaku: phenology
What's your name?
Araragi Karen.
The "small village" radical, with the kanji for possibility.
Good, twice.
"Ki," like a sapling.
And my given name means "to admire the flame."
Karen.
An excellent name.
Be grateful to your parents.
So, which are you?
Do you want to learn a charm?
Or have one undone?
The former is 10,000 yen. The latter, 20,000.
Neither.
I've come here to punch you!
To punch me?
So the message you sent me was a fake, and this is a trap.
I see.
Well done.
Of course, I don't believe that you were the one who did it.
I can't imagine a simpleton like you
Black
Unnumbered Cut
being able to find me.
Not many people could.
Only someone who's a touch abnormal could get this far.
What you're doing is a giant pain in the butt.
You don't need me to elaborate, do you?
A pain?
I'm giving you kids what you want.
How you use it is your responsibility.
Our responsibility?
How is it our responsibility?
How dare you?!
You're ruining people's relationships...
What are you thinking?
What am I thinking?
Quite a deep question.
Unfortunately, I'll have to respond with a shallow answer.
I'm thinking about the money, naturally.
Money?
Money makes the world go 'round.
Akasegawa
Bank of Damaged Goods
10,000
Yen
Counterfeit
Bank Note
I suppose you've come here out of some primitive sense of justice.
Ten Thousand
Akasegawa
Bank of Damaged Goods
10,000
Yen
Ten Thousand
Counterfeit
Bank Note
But that was a mistake.
You could have had someone pay you 100,000 yen for this.
The lesson for you here is that
it's never worth working for free.
No one hired me!
I'm not here because someone asked me to be!
Akasegawa
Ten Thousand
Counterfeit
Bank Note
10,000
Yen
Bank of Damaged Goods
I see...
Then you should have had someone ask you.
Even if someone had, I wouldn't have taken their money!
Bank of Damaged Goods
So young...
I'm not at all jealous, though.
What's wrong? You're shaking, Araragi.
I'm not shaking...
Akasegawa
Ten Thousand
Counterfeit
Bank Note
10,000
Yen
Bank of Damaged Goods
Araragi, you've heard what I wanted.
Now it's your turn.
What do you want?
I told you already.
I came here to punch you!
Just to punch me?
I'll kick you, too!
Violence, then?
Force!
And I'll make you stop this.
Selling this crap to middle schoolers?
What are you thinking?
And you call yourself an adult?!
I'm an adult, yes.
And of course I'm selling it to them.
I'm a con man.
Aren't you embarrassed, taking advantage of middle schoolers?!
Not at all.
Children are easy to fool.
That's all.
But, Araragi, if you want to stop me,
punches and kicks are useless.
The fastest way would be to bring money.
My target for this little business is three million.
3,000,000 Yen
I've spent over two months setting it up.
Any less, and it wouldn't be worth my time.
And you call yourself human?
Unfortunately, I am human, yes.
I'm willing to sacrifice my life to protect what's dear to me.
Just as you fill your heart through good deeds,
I fill my bank account with evil ones.
Is there really a difference?
A-A difference?
No, there's no difference at all.
Your activities may make someone happier.
But the same is true if I take the money I've earned
and use it to grease the gears of a capitalist economy.
The lesson for you here is that
just as there isn't a problem that can't be solved with righteousness,
there isn't a problem that can't be solved with money.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
The same is true of my victims, yes?
They paid me in money.
This means that they recognized money as an object of value.
Red
Unnumbered Cut
Is the same not true of you?
Or did you not pay in money when you bought that jacket?
D-Don't talk about the jacket!
Just give me your answer.
Do you want to be punched?
Or...
I don't want to be punched.
Nor do I want to be kicked.
I dislike pain.
So here's a present for you—a bee.
It's working quite well.
You must have an active imagination.
The lesson for you here is to assume
that any person you see is a con man.
Learn to doubt others.
Did you think I would beg for forgiveness?
Then you're just a fool.
If you want me to have a change of heart, bring some cash.
I'd be willing to discuss it for ten million.
W-What did you do?
What did you do to me?!
Something bad.
Of course, nothing is free.
I'll take money for it.
4,000 yen? I suppose that will do.
I'll throw in our little chat as a bonus.
I suppose I can leave some change for the train fare home—
Oh, you have a pass.
Then you won't need this change.
In a moment, the poison will take hold, and you'll be able to move.
I recommend using your phone to call for help.
In the meantime, I'll make my escape.
Of course, I'll continue what I was doing.
But from now on, I'll avoid meeting my customers directly.
You've taught me an excellent lesson.
Farewell.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Araragi-kun, are you upset?
About what?
Well, you know...
I was the one who tracked him down.
Are you mad about what happened to Karen-chan?
I wouldn't say that I'm mad.
But I'd like to say that if you were going to help the Fire Sisters, you should have told me.
But wouldn't you have gotten mad?
And if I decide I want to be friends with Karen-chan and Tsukihi-chan, isn't it my choice?
It is your choice.
Yup.
But as an apology for not telling you about Karen-chan and Tsukihi-chan,
you can have this ticket!
What's this?
This ticket entitles you to touch my breasts whenever you want, for as long as you like.
It's yours.
Seriously?
Yep! Seriously.
But if you use it, I'll hate you forever.
Then it's useless!
Well, that aside,
don't be too mean to Karen-chan and Tsukihi-chan.
It's fine.
Don't worry about it.
I realize they aren't just doing it for fun.
I know we've talked before about your differences.
But still, they are a bit like you.
They share a resemblance?
Not on the outside, on the inside.
I guess I'm one to talk, though.
Tell me about it.
Of course, your family and mine are different.
Oshino-san...
I wonder what Oshino-san's up to right now?
I don't know.
But he's watching over us from somewhere.
He'd probably easily fix whatever's wrong with Karen-chan if he were here.
From what Shinobu said, the flame wreathe bee
is a very low-level monster.
Shinobu-chan?
Flame wreathe bee?
A flame wreathe bee, huh?
Well, I'm glad to see you've made up with Shinobu-chan.
I'm not upset about it, but...
The reason Oshino-san left was that he thought he could leave Shinobu-chan to you, right?
Really, it would've made sense if you'd reconciled just after the cultural festival.
I guess that means it's taken a long time.
You could say I've been slacking on the job.
You haven't been slacking at all.
I know that very well.
You know everything, don't you?
I don't know everything.
I just know what I know.
The real effort in a fight comes after you've made up.
Keep that in mind.
I can go the rest of the way myself.
Take my bike.
I'll lend it to you.
You're sure?
I'll take it, I guess.
Okay, then. Thanks for letting me take it.
I'll give it back tomorrow.
Yeah.
Get this solved tonight.
You have to start studying again tomorrow.
It's good that you're being a brother,
but don't forget that you're a high school student, too!
Don't make such a big deal out of this, Nii-chan.
This is why I didn't want to tell you.
People should keep their mouths shut.
It's just a fever.
Shut up. You're sick, so shush and do as I say.
Want to eat something?
Canned peaches?
No appetite.
I see.
I'm gonna let down your hair.
I want to take a bath.
This sweat feels awful.
Your hair.
Go ahead.
A bath isn't happening,
but I'll wipe down your body.
Thanks.
Not that I like it.
Right.
Then take your clothes off.
Time  Temperature   Menu
Start
Manual
setting
Cancel
Favorites
Measure
dish
Finish
Manual
Auto
Water
Microwave
Oven
Grill
Heated steam
Steam
Health
mode
Don't push
this button
Hey, I said to take off your clothes.
Sorry, Nii-chan.
I'm tired...
Take my clothes off.
Wipe me down, put 'em back on.
Why, you...
My brother saw me
completely naked and now
I'm so embarrassed.
–Karen
My brother saw me completely naked and now I'm so embarrassed.
Why is it a haiku?
Because I'm embarrassed!
You dance around half naked when you get out of the bath. I don't wanna hear it.
I'm not dancing! That's aerobics!
I'll wipe down your back.
Turn over.
Too lazy. Turn me over.
Damn it...
I screwed this up.
I know strength is more important than being right. I didn't need you to tell me.
But you can't get strong all of a sudden.
However,
that doesn't mean you can just ignore all the bad stuff you see until you're strong.
The blood of justice flows through me,
and it tells me to punish evil.
You just like punching people.
That's what I think.
I'm sure it all looks like a game to you.
But Kaiki...
Kaiki Deishuu...
Tsukihi-chan already told you why he was spreading those
weird charms and curses around the middle schools, right?
That's right. It was for money.
He spread hatred...
Fear...
And then, he took advantage of it to take money without actually doing anything.
And when I asked him if he wasn't ashamed,
here's what he said.
Without a trace of shame, he said,
"Children are easier to fool."
Easier to fool...
Tsukihi-chan's friend... Sengoku, was it?
She really didn't want to talk about it,
but whatever happened, didn't you save her?
But she was one of the lucky ones.
Some kids went to Kaiki for help, not knowing he was the source of the rumors,
and got caught shoplifting trying to get the money he demanded from them.
Could you have let that happen?
Could you have looked them in the eye and said,
"I'm not strong yet, so I won't do anything?"
He told me money was everything.
I didn't think anyone like that existed outside of manga.
I mean, money is important.
But aren't there other things that matter, too?
Sold
Out
First Love
¥248
New Product!
Love
¥298
Sold
Out
Talent
¥284
Like love!
Love
¥298
Tax Included
Our opinions overlapped.
Money isn't everything.
It's just mostly everything!
Okay, maybe not.
Nii-chan, Tsukihi-chan and I are serious about this.
We won't stop here.
If this happens again, we'll do the same thing.
This time, I may have lost.
But I didn't lose mentally.
And next time, I'll win.
I'll keep it up until I win. I'll try, even if I don't win.
The outcome isn't all that's important. Right, Nii-chan?
Lose the fight but keep the high ground, huh?
That doesn't sound like much of a warrior's code.
You can lose the fight and get thrown into the dirt,
but if you don't lose to yourself, it isn't a loss.
That's my warrior's code.
But as long as you stay like that,
those around you will suffer.
That's why you'll never grow up.
I'm already grown up.
Look at these boobs!
Not even half Hanekawa's size.
What of it?
Tsubasa-san is that big?
She's the real thing.
I think you know that.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Honestly,
I'd prefer if you didn't hang out with Hanekawa.
But I guess this is a good chance.
From now on, you should start learning from her.
Don't move. It's hard to wipe you down.
It's fine now. I feel much better.
We're almost done. Don't stop now.
I don't want to get you sick.
Get me sick?
W-Wait a second.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Shinobu.
What? It's almost time for bed.
Then, one thing before bed...
Is there any way to transfer her illness to me?
It's more of a oddity's poison than an illness.
And it was given to her deliberately.
So wouldn't it be possible for her to give it to me?
So you're saying you'll take her illness?
There is a way.
But honestly, I can't recommend it.
Or it would be more accurate to say
I certainly wouldn't prefer it.
I understand there's a risk.
I don't know if "risk" is the right word.
Well, I suppose it's an urban legend.
I think the kid used totally different words to describe it.
What?
That's pretty vague. And not like you at all.
Well, I don't know...
Whether or not it's something that would be allowed, I couldn't say.
I don't know what you're talking about, but of course it would.
If there's any way to alleviate her suffering,
we should take it, whatever it is.
Very true.
Do what you will, then.
Nii-chan,
I don't know if you went to the bathroom or what,
but you should've at least dressed me first.
Karen-chan.
I'm going to kiss you now.
I can see you checking out that girl in the school uniform
You're making it obvious as hell
I mean come on, I'm standing right here
What do you even think you're doing?
Don't think that I'm going to be here by your side forever
We know that one day,
Someone, somewhere is going to take me
And then I'll be gone, do you understand that?
And when that time comes it'll be too late
Even if you cry, it won't be my problem
And making that face won't get you anywhere
Really, you're easy
And I can't help getting irritated, you know?
Preview
Script: Nisio Isin
Illustrations: Haritama Hiroki
'Sup! I'm Karen!
We're the fire sisters!
I don't like the thought of being alone.
I think we've all caught a cold before,
but don't you think the characters used to write it are a bit peculiar?
compared to the
characters who
changed their
appearance
I feel like I don't stand out much
That's not true.
The wind character is read like that on its own, so what's 'malice' doing after it?
Isn't the 'malice' unneeded? Wouldn't it be read the same without it?
To make the most of my
strong points,
I'll go learn under a karate master.
What bringing
this on?
I know I'm being fussy here,
and maybe they just wanted to make sure there's a difference
between just wind and cold, which are both pronounced the same,
but why didn't they just change what they called the common cold?
Roar
Waterfall
Bear
Grr
Mountain
I was too naive!
It's going to air soon!
And isn't the on'yomi reading 'fuuja' anyway?
Oh, fuuja!
Whoa, that sounds so cool and mysterious.
I'll shave off one
eyebrow and get
myself
psyched up!
What?!
Razor!
Final and ultimate secret of the Araragi school of self-defense!
Fuuja!
Next time! Karen Bee, Part 6!
Next Episode
Karen Bee         Part Six
That reminds me, summer cold and summer wind also sound the same, don't they?
We're the new-look sisters!