Black
Unnumbered Cut
Karen Bee
Part Six
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Six
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Six
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Six
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Six
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Six
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part Six
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Xem Trước
Script: Nisio Isin
Illustrations: Haritama Hiroki
We're the fire sisters!
I'm worried about them...
Perfect!
Go help them out!
What?!
You're the assistant
we asked for?
Resume
All right, let's start with patrolling the town.
Next Episode
Karen Bee      Part Seven
Oh, no! We're lost!