Butterfly
Bee
Red Salmon
Correct answer
Time
Passes
Araragi Karen and Araragi Tsukihi, my little sisters, are the central element
of this story, though I very much doubt there would be any group of people in this world interested in it.
Also, even if I suppose there was such an extraordinary demand, I would not want to go into thorough detail about the two of them.
However if they were not my little sisters, most probably they would never have anything to do with me, and even if they did, I am as I am, I would just ignore them.
Well, that being said, it is only fair that I honestly admit that my thinking like that is most likely a result of my inferiority complex, jealousy and bias towards
them. In sharp contrast to me, who spent his high school days lazily and therefore fell behind, Karen and Tsukihi are doing great.
But I want to say it out loud.
While they have not fallen behind, they are problem children, and though they are persons of character,
at the same time their characters are failing.
The Fire Sisters of Tsuganoki Second Middle School.
Araragi Karen is the fighter of the Fire Sisters and Araragi Tsukihi is the brains.
Like that the two of them spent their days like a helper squad, or a team to make the world better,
or something along those lines, acting like great friends of justice.
But I, as their relative, can assure you that what they are doing is not something so great.
It is merely an outlet for their energy.
Araragi Karen and Araragi Tsukihi.
The acts of the two of them, of the Fire Sisters, are really merely acting like great friends of justice.
My dearest little sisters. You two are hopeless impostors.
Thứ Bảy, ngày 29 tháng 7
Reference
Physics
Flashback
Eloquence of Successful People
Protect Your Heart from Sickness:
Hear Your Heart's Call for Help
Teen Communication
Keep Your Opinion Straight:   How to Debate
The Art of High Quality Lies
The Book of Reading Other People's Minds
My Identity
How To Keep Your Soul Healthy
"Can't Go On" Goodbye to Conversation?
The Five
Secrets of
Brainwashing
How to Talk to Have Everyone on Your Side
Protect Your Heart from Sickness:
Hear Your Heart's Call for Help
Teen Communication
How to Debate
The Art of High Quality Lies
The Book of Reading Other People's Minds
My Identity
Quarrel
Flash
back
Araragi Koyomi
Lo ve
Hachikuji
No Light Vehicles
No Boys Allowed
No Old Men
Beware of Bears
Love
Sold
Out
First Love
¥248
New Product!
Love
¥298
Sold
Out
Talent
¥284
Love
¥298
Tax Included
Sold
Out
First Love
¥248
New Product!
Love
¥298
Sold
Out
Talent
¥284
Love
¥298
Tax Included
Courage Series
Cảnh Báo
Đất Tư Nhân
nghiêm cấm đánh golf
hay bóng chày.
Cảnh Báo
Đất Tư Nhân
nghiêm cấm đánh golf
hay bóng chày.
Cảnh Báo
Đất Tư Nhân
nghiêm cấm đánh golf
hay bóng chày.
Cảnh Báo
Đất Tư Nhân
nghiêm cấm đánh golf
hay bóng chày.
Next Episode
Karen Bee        Part Two