I apologize for this jarring and unexpected development,
but it appears I have been kidnapped.
This happened ten days into summer vacation, on July 29th.
No, it's possible that it's already the 30th.
Oh, you're awake, Araragi-kun.
I'm glad.
I was worried you might have died.
Are you all right?
Does the back of your head hurt?
Senjougahara, get these handcuffs off me.
No.
I knew it! You did this!
I see.
Interesting theory,
assuming you have proof.
I guessed the minute I saw you chose to confine me at this cram school.
Now take off the handcuffs!
No.
No. Also, I can't. I've thrown away the key.
Seriously?
I also threw away the antidote.
You poisoned me, too?!
That was a lie.
Though it might come true if you don't do as I say.
Float like a butterfly, sting like a butterfly!
Butterflies don't sting!
I said it wrong.
Good for you, to be able to point out my mistake.
Take pride in this moment forever.
What's this new, avant-garde method of admitting your mistakes?
The correct word was "bee."
Butterfly
Bee
Bee poison is strong, isn't it?
Don't worry.
Araragi-kun,
I'll protect you.
You won't die.
Because I'll protect you.
I'd prefer to enjoy this conversation
with no unnecessary Evangelion references.
And, um, Gahara-san?
I'm hungry...
And kinda thirsty.
Want to get something to eat?
I expected a wormlike fool like yourself might say that,
so I brought several items with me.
Did you?
Then give me something to drink.
You want something to drink?
Well, I guess...
But I'm going to drink it.
It's good.
What's with that look of longing?
No one said they were giving it to you.
Or did you think I'd feed it to you, mouth-to-mouth?
My, Araragi-kun...
You're so naughty.
In this situation, only Kanbaru would come up with that!
Yeah?
Remember when we were making out the other day?
That's not something you bring up in this situation!
All right, then.
If you absolutely must drink it, I'll let you.
I absolutely must drink it.
Has this man no pride?
To say something so humiliating,
from a simple desire for water.
Wouldn't it be better for you if you just died?
She really seems to be enjoying this.
Very well.
Since you're so insistent,
so pathetic, that I can't bear to look at you,
I'll give you some water, out of sympathy.
Be grateful,
water-drinking bird.
"Water-drinking bird" isn't really an insult, is it?
Lick it.
What's wrong?
You're thirsty, aren't you?
So stretch out your tongue,
and naughtily lick it, like a giraffe.
Hey, Senjougahara.
What?
Aren't you thirsty?
Or was that a lie?
Liars should be punished.
I'll lick it!
I'll totally lick it!
Please let me lick it!
How pathetic.
The epitome of pathetic.
No normal person would do this, just for some water.
I'm sure you're a pervert who just enjoys licking girls' fingers, right?
Senjougahara-san was enjoying herself so much, I thought she'd explode.
Such a wonderful picture. I want to set it as my cell phone wallpaper.
Yeah? Glad to hear it.
Then, next I'd like a rice ball.
All right.
I'm in one of my rare generous moods.
What do you want in it?
It doesn't matter.
An apathetic reply.
Do you prefer bread?
That's not really it.
And as near as I can tell, you haven't bought any bread.
That's true. I only brought rice balls.
I won't request something you don't have.
If they have no bread, then let them give me cake.
Too tyrannical!
Well, my parents did raise me like a queen.
You mean like a princess!
Red Salmon
Correct answer
Time
Passes
I didn't have much time today, so I got lunch from a convenience store.
But don't worry, Araragi-kun.
Starting tomorrow, I'll make your meals myself.
What is this?
Her motives remain unclear.
Oh, right.
Her motives are totally clear.
Don't worry.
Araragi-kun,
I'll protect you.
To protect me, right?
She's serious.
Probably.
By the way, Senjougahara.
How am I supposed to use the bathroom here?
Don't worry.
I'll change your diaper.
Didn't you know?
I love you, Araragi-kun.
So much that I could embrace you without hesitation,
even if you were entirely covered in feces.
Including your brain, I will manage your entire body,
from ingestion to excretion.
Her love is too extreme!
Even now, whenever I'm with you
I become as anxious as ever
I'm pretending to look out the window
but what I'm really staring at is your reflection
"What parts of me are what you fell in love with all that time ago?"
"Am I still the right me? Did I mess it all up?"
Going back and going forth
Going round and round and      round
round
And with the first thing you say,
I forget about absolutely all of it
And with the second thing you say,
I start to want more and more
When you look at me, I can breathe
As all my worries just seem to slip away
Impostory
Araragi Karen and Araragi Tsukihi, my little sisters, are the central element
of this story, though I very much doubt there would be any group of people in this world interested in it.
Also, even if I suppose there was such an extraordinary demand, I would not want to go into thorough detail about the two of them.
However if they were not my little sisters, most probably they would never have anything to do with me, and even if they did, I am as I am, I would just ignore them.
Well, that being said, it is only fair that I honestly admit that my thinking like that is most likely a result of my inferiority complex, jealousy and bias towards
them. In sharp contrast to me, who spent his high school days lazily and therefore fell behind, Karen and Tsukihi are doing great.
But I want to say it out loud.
While they have not fallen behind, they are problem children, and though they are persons of character,
at the same time their characters are failing.
The Fire Sisters of Tsuganoki Second Middle School.
Araragi Karen is the fighter of the Fire Sisters and Araragi Tsukihi is the brains.
Like that the two of them spent their days like a helper squad, or a team to make the world better,
or something along those lines, acting like great friends of justice.
But I, as their relative, can assure you that what they are doing is not something so great.
It is merely an outlet for their energy.
Araragi Karen and Araragi Tsukihi.
The acts of the two of them, of the Fire Sisters, are really merely acting like great friends of justice.
My dearest little sisters. You two are hopeless impostors.
Karen Bee
Part One
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part One
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part One
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part One
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part One
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part One
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Karen Bee
Part One
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Saturday, July 29th
Morning
Scene No. 131
Over summer break, I'm being tutored each weekday and Saturday by Senjougahara,
Saturday, July 29th
Reference
one of the highest-performing students at our school,
Physics
and by Hanekawa, the very highest-performing.
But on that Saturday, July 29th,
Hanekawa, with whom I was to study...
Flashback
"Something came up that I can't get out of.
I'll make it up to you in exactly two days!"
Black
Unnumbered Cut
And so, I'm bored.
Oh, Onii-chan...
You said you're not getting tutored today, right?
Yeah.
Hey, where is she?
She?
My bigger little sister.
Karen-chan's out.
Don't get into any trouble, you two.
I resent that. We aren't planning anything.
You're always this way.
You always treat us like children.
You worry too much.
I'm not worried.
I just don't trust you.
Aren't those the same thing?
No.
Worry and trust are two entirely different things.
The only real difference is...
Don't stop talking halfway through!
So, where'd the bigger little sister go?
I told you, she isn't in any trouble.
In fact, she went to go help people out of trouble.
That's trouble.
Onii-chan, just don't interfere in middle school kids' fights. It's lame.
Fights are a valid form of communication, in their own way.
Well, it sounds right when you put it like that.
It isn't that fights are wrong, per se.
It's that people simply don't know the proper way to fight.
Eloquence of Successful People
Protect Your Heart from Sickness:
Hear Your Heart's Call for Help
Teen Communication
Keep Your Opinion Straight:   How to Debate
The Art of High Quality Lies
The Book of Reading Other People's Minds
My Identity
How To Keep Your Soul Healthy
"Can't Go On" Goodbye to Conversation?
The Five
Secrets of
Brainwashing
How to Talk to Have Everyone on Your Side
Protect Your Heart from Sickness:
Hear Your Heart's Call for Help
Teen Communication
How to Debate
The Art of High Quality Lies
The Book of Reading Other People's Minds
My Identity
Quarrel
But the fights you two get involved with are always violent.
I refuse to believe that's the right way to fight.
Just shut up!
I don't know!
I don't know anything!
I don't know what's going on with the bigger sister,
the littler sister, or the middle sister!
I don't have a middle sister...
This is why it's never worth it to worry about either of you.
Jeez...
I won't tell you to grow up,
but at least keep quiet.
I don't want to hear that from you.
Well, I suppose that of the two,
the latter is more difficult.
Anyone can grow up, just by aging.
But still, I wouldn't want them as quiet as Sengoku.
Oh, right. Sengoku...
Flash
back
Come over to my house sometime.
Sure.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Come to think of it,
it's been quite a while since then.
This is a good chance.
H-Hello?!
This is Shengoku!
Koyomi-oniichan, it's been a while.
What's up?
Araragi Koyomi
Sorry it's so abrupt,
but remember when I said I'd come over?
I was wondering if today might be good.
If it isn't a good day—
No...
Today, today, today!
Actually, I'm busy every day but today.
I see.
If you're busy every day but today,
today is our only option.
How about now?
Sure!
Actually, no time but now will work.
Then I'll come over now.
Hey! So...
Bye!
I'll watch the house.
No, you're coming, as well.
What?
We're going to Sengoku's, so of course you're coming.
I thought for sure you'd go alone.
And I'm certain that's what Sen-chan is thinking...
Really?
No way.
Go by yourself.
I'm sure she'd prefer that.
Anyway...
A
N
Anyway...
Y
W
Anyway...
A
I won't interfere with a friend's feeling of love.
Even if it's unrequited.
Lo ve
Love?
She never said she'd love for me to come over.
She just asked me to.
Unlike you two, she's polite.
By the way, Onii-chan...
Do you believe that boys and girls can be friends?
Sure.
I'm Sengoku's friend!
I see.
Then I guess that works.
Anyway, get going.
Fine.
Then I'll go on my own.
Watch the house while I'm gone.
See ya, then.
One last thing before you go.
You've totally stopped sparring with Karen-chan.
How come?
She's gotten too good at karate lately.
Like, way too good.
I'd lose in a straight-up fight.
Even though she's taller,
I should still be stronger.
But I guess I can't defeat a martial arts practitioner.
That explains things with Karen-chan,
but when I freaked out a minute ago, you backed off.
Dealing with you has gotten a lot easier.
Well, I guess so.
I mean, from our perspective,
it's good, because it's easier to get our way.
But you know,
really...
Don't just grow up and leave us behind.
It'd be boring that way.
Actually, you guys never knew this,
but I turned into a vampire.
Well, I turned back.
But it changed me. So it's possible...
And I mean possible, not certain,
that if I got into a real fight with you,
Red
Unnumbered Cut
I could end up killing you both.
So I'm trying to avoid that.
Yeah, right. How am I supposed to tell them that?
Hey, it's Hachikuji.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Hachikuji
But I promised to go to Sengoku's...
And I don't really like that elementary school brat, anyway.
Honestly, I really don't like her.
I hate her.
We're not even close enough that I'd talk to her if I saw her.
But yeah, I guess as a high schooler,
it's kind of sad for me to act that way toward an elementary school girl.
Honestly, I'm not happy to see her at all.
But I suppose a bare minimum of courtesy demands that I maintain appearances.
I'm such a sap.
Hachikuji!
I've missed you!
I haven't seen you for a while,
so I thought you'd gone away somewhere!
I was so worried!
So let me touch you more.
Let me hug you more.
Let me lick you more!
Come on, stay put!
You're making it hard to take your panties off!
Ow!
What are you doing?
W-Wait, Hachikuji!
Look, it's me!
It's Araragi...
Yomiko-san!
That's depressingly close.
But, Hachikuji,
I'd prefer you not call me the name of a paper-using secret agent
for the British Library who lives in a book-filled Jinbouchou building.
My name is Araragi Koyomi.
No Light Vehicles
But that aside, Araragi-san,
where are you going today?
Nowhere special.
No Boys Allowed
Searching for new Araragi harem members?
I never founded such a creepy group!
One of the original members, Oshino-san, has graduated now.
It'll be a difficult gap to fill.
Even assuming this so-called Araragi harem's existence,
why would Oshino be a member?
He's an old guy in a floral shirt!
No Old Men
Add too many members,
and the story will be hard to follow.
Beware of Bears
So be careful.
Well, I told you about Sengoku, right?
That girl I used to know.
I'm going over to her place today.
Given that, you seemed rather unhappy.
Did I?
I looked that unhappy?
Yeah!
Like a story that joked about how it would never be animated,
and then by some fluke, actually was.
Your awkwardness was reminiscent of that.
My face was hardly that specific!
Well, I can understand that you'd be wary of unexpected happiness.
But any time you enter a new arena,
there's something to be gained.
Something to be gained? Like what?
In a word...
Money.
Uh, isn't there anything more?
Is there really anything else in the world?
Sure!
Like you know...
Love!
Love
Wuh? Love?
Oh, yeah! I know love.
The convenience store was selling it.
Sold
Out
First Love
¥248
New Product!
Love
¥298
Sold
Out
Talent
¥284
They were selling it?! At the convenience store?
Yup, for 298 yen.
Love
¥298
Tax Included
A bargain!
Talk of money aside, Araragi-san,
I've been looking forward to this.
What kind of dance will we do during the ED?
It's a given that we're dancing?
I'm hoping for something like in Cat's Eye,
nice and sexy!
You're okay with just silhouettes?!
Anyway, that's not it, Hachikuji.
Oh, right... I guess I can tell you.
You know I'm actually a vampire, right?
I see, Shuraragi-san.
That name's pretty cool,
and honestly, I'd like to change mine to it.
But Hachikuji,
I've told you over and over,
my name is Araragi.
Sorry! I bit my tongue.
No, you did it on purpose.
I bit into a tart!
It wasn't on purpose?!
Seen the Family Mart?
No, I don't know where the convenience store is!
Is it love?
Sold
Out
First Love
¥248
New Product!
Love
¥298
Sold
Out
Talent
¥284
Are you going to buy love?
Love
¥298
Tax Included
For 298 yen?!
I see, a vampire.
But what about it?
Well, it's really hard to tell my family about it, you know?
But I'm not sure it's something I could hide forever.
I don't think it's really necessary to just come out and tell them.
I think keeping a secret or two from your family is natural.
Hachikuji?
For one thing, sharing your secret with someone
means you involve them in your problems.
It may make things easier for you,
but your family could end up suffering for it.
That's true, isn't it?
Right now, what you need is the courage to keep your secret to yourself!
That sounds very wise.
Well, I'm just making it sound positive by adding the word "courage" to it.
Really, it's just a normal secret.
Too honest!
You can make almost anything sound positive by adding the word "courage."
That can't be right.
I refuse to believe that Japanese is structured that way.
Shall I demonstrate?
Bring it.
If you can prove your point to my satisfaction,
I'll do a handstand, right here.
A handstand?
Yes...
Like getting on your knees to bow, but better.
And if you can't satisfy me,
then you have to do a handstand here,
wearing your skirt!
Your kiddy panties will be exposed to public view
until I allow you to stop!
Very well.
I accept your challenge.
I praise your guts, if nothing else.
You're like a phoenix to the flame, Araragi-san.
No, I'm nothing as cool as that.
We'll start with warm-ups.
Courage Series
The courage to lie to your lover.
Not bad...
All you're doing is simply lying,
but tacking "courage" onto it makes it sound like you're lying for your lover's sake.
Even though she hasn't said anything suggesting that.
The courage to betray your comrades.
What?!
Amazing!
The end result is that you've betrayed your comrades.
But that gives the impression that you've somehow protected them.
Even though she hasn't said anything suggesting that!
The courage to be a lazy bum.
Wh-What?
It really can do anything!
You're just meaninglessly whiling away your life,
but that makes it sound like you've positioned yourself in poverty, all for some greater goal.
Even though she hasn't said anything, anything at all, suggesting that!
B-But I cannot admit defeat here!
The courage to admit defeat.
I admit my defeat!
I was lulled by the awesomeness of your words
into admitting my own defeat!
And all I did was admit defeat...
Japanese is really simple!
Now, Araragi-san.
Show me something better than getting on your knees to bow.
Very well.
I have the courage to do a handstand!
Seeing someone your age doing a handstand is actually kind of pathetic...
You can stop.
I said you could stop, Araragi-san.
Actually, please stop, Araragi-san.
I'm embarrassed just being next to you.
Why continue your handstand as if you were honoring the final request of your deceased friend?
Well, you know...
I was just thinking that even if I'm the one doing the handstand,
from this angle I still get to see your panties.
Araragi-san, you are a pervert!
The courage to accept the label of pervert!
So cool!
You're so cool that I'm tempted to have the courage to reveal my panties!
Especially the way you persist even after I kicked you in the face!
I can't believe the technology I developed has now been turned against me...
So ironic.
You grew overconfident, Hachikuji!
I have mastered your secret technique!
Oh, no.
I may have created a monster!
But I do apologize for calling them kiddy panties.
I never expected you'd be wearing translucent black panties.
What?!
What are you saying?
Take a closer look!
Don't say that!
It'll ruin my image!
I've responded to consumer demand
and am wearing kiddy panties!
They have a bunny on them, right?
I can't see any bunnies.
If you want me to see them, you have to make it easier.
L-Like this?
Oh, yeah.
We were talking about the need to keep the supernatural a secret, right?
You see, Araragi-san,
in a way, the supernatural is what's behind the curtain.
Behind the curtain?
Normally, you only need to see what's happening on stage.
That's how reality works.
If you don't already know,
then it's best that you don't find out.
Actually, learning about the supernatural
only increases the number of things you don't know.
I see.
So, Araragi-san...
If your family should ever find themselves unfortunately backstage,
you can guide them out.
But until then, the answer is to do nothing.
I see.
Warning:
Private Area.
Golf, Baseball etc.
is forbidden!
Anyway, we've been talking a while.
Sorry for stopping you, Hachikuji.
It's fine.
I'm always basically lost.
That's not...
In a way,
I guess I was just walking around, saying,
"Isn't Araragi-san's house here?
I haven't seen him in a while!
Maybe I can see him again."
Yeah.
Well, bye!
Yeah, let's meet again.
Hey, Hachikuji.
You aren't going to disappear, are you?
Because, you know, Oshino's gone.
I just wondered if one day you're going to vanish like he did.
You spend so much time worrying about others.
The only people you ever impose your problems on are Shinobu-san and me.
I'm honored, really.
Hachikuji...
Then let me ask you a question, Araragi-san.
If I'm ever in really bad trouble again,
would you help me?
Sure, I would.
Of course I would.
I won't give anyone else enough time to save you.
I can talk to you about my problems?
If you don't, I'll get mad!
That's just like you.
I'm sure there's a reason that,
even after I stopped being lost,
I stayed here.
I won't leave until I know what that reason is.
The reason, huh?
Well, even if I do go away someday,
before I do, I'll come to say goodbye.
I see...
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Okay, then you do that.
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Yeah.
I'd be scared of having you mad at me, y'know?
I can see you checking out that girl in the school uniform
You're making it obvious as hell
I mean come on, I'm standing right here
What do you even think you're doing?
Don't think that I'm going to be here by your side forever
We know that one day,
Someone, somewhere is going to take me
And then I'll be gone, do you understand that?
And when that time comes it'll be too late
Even if you cry, it won't be my problem
And making that face won't get you anywhere
Really, you're easy
And I can't help getting irritated, you know?
Script: Nisio Isin
Illustrations: Haritama Hiroki
Preview
It's Nadeko, yo!
I'm Karen!
This preview goes out to all the brothers out there!
I'm Tsukihi!
Today we will write "Twister Game" in kanji!
Hooray!
The TV show airing where the Fire Sisters
have the starring role!
Nisemonogatari!
I would pick the "tsui" from "shoot down" and combine it with "mister" to get "twister"!
The possibilities!
Um...
Just how many misters have been shot through the heart during that game?
The profit!
Um...
Personally, I want to be known as an ace pilot someday.
Now let's
go raid the
public airwaves!
Um...
Here we go, check it out!
Next time! Karen Bee, Part 2!
Next Episode
Karen Bee        Part Two
I feel like all that was out of character...
What?
The episode previews
only stream online?!