Red
Unnumbered Cut
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Three
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Three
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Three
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Three
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Three
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Three
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Tsukihi Phoenix
Part Three
Font used in the video: HGP Mincho B
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Hoạt Cảnh số    171
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Yellow
Black
Unnumbered Cut
Xem Trước
Script: Nisio Isin
Illustrations: Haritama Hiroki
We're the fire—
Silent
I saw it on TV!
I want in on the action!
Say that earlier!
What the hell is
going on here, fire sisters?
Whoa! Onī-chan!
You two
are still fakes!
We're sorry
Huh? Is that the script?
Slipping Out
A Technicolor Animated Movie
in All Theaters
Kizumonogatari
Production Underway
Starring Araragi Koyomi
Our hearts are one!
We're the fire sisters!
Next Episode
Tsukihi Phoenix    Part Four
You'll see us again soon!