Let's
end
our
story
by
revealing
the
true
identity
of
Araragi
Tsukihi.
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
We'll
end
the
story
of
me
and
my
beloved
companions
with
the
tale
of my
bratty,
annoying,
smaller
little
sister.
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
Araragi
Tsukihi.
One
of the
Fire
Sisters.
The
younger
little
sister.
The
smaller
little
sister.
In her
second
year of
middle
school.
Born
in
April.
Age fourteen.
Blood type B.
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
sjdlsjdlsjldjs
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
sjdlsjdlsjldjs
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
sjdlsjdlsjldjs
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
sjdlsjdlsjldjs
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
sjdlsjdlsjldjs
Sly.
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
hsdjkshdkjshsd
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
hsdjkshdkjshsd
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
hsdjkshdkjshsd
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
hsdjkshdkjshsd
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
hsdjkshdkjshsd
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
hsdjkshdkjshsd
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
hsdjkshdkjshsd
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
hsdjkshdkjshsd
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
hsdjkshdkjshsd
dhshdskdhs
sddjsdss
hsdjkshdkjshsd
Impostory
I feel like I need to emphasize here
that our relationship is not a particularly close one, for a brother and sister.
If you talk about my other, youngest sister, Tsukihi, and Karen together,
they really do have close relationship, probably since they were born only a year apart from one another.
But, unfortunately, I wouldn't say that I'm that close with them.
More appropriately, you could say we're on bad terms.
Maybe go so far as to say "dislike."
Karen and Tsukihi, on the one hand, are constantly rebelling against me,
and I, on the other, am getting fed up with their childish ideas.
I especially can't deal with
them playing hero, calling themselves the Fire Sisters.
It seems that even the event with Kaiki Deishuu
wasn't enough to make them change.
I feel like I need to emphasize here
that our relationship is not a particularly close one, for a brother and sister.
If you talk about my other, youngest sister, Tsukihi, and Karen together,
they really do have close relationship, probably since they were born only a year apart from one another.
But, unfortunately, I wouldn't say that I'm that close with them.
More appropriately, you could say we're on bad terms.
Maybe go so far as to say "dislike."
Karen and Tsukihi, on the one hand, are constantly rebelling against me,
and I, on the other, am getting fed up with their childish ideas.
I especially can't deal with
them playing hero, calling themselves the Fire Sisters.
It seems that even the event with Kaiki Deishuu
wasn't enough to make them change.
Success   Achievement
Sole
Reference
English Drills
500 words that are easy to memorize
This is the unofficial fan club, made by your host, a huge Kanbaru Suruga fan.
It is unofficial. There are no dues.
It's a place for comrades who secretly love Kanbaru Suruga to gather.
!!No trolling!!
Kanbaru Souer
Closed
3min. 24s
3min. 23s
3min. 21s
3min. 20s
3min. 17s
3min. 16s
3min. 14s
3min. 13s
3min. 10s
Tsukihi
Phoenix
Chapter
Closed